<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>anything goes with emma chamberlain</title>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>quitting nicotine update (it’s not going well)</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4M831MCuqbt45tWXa7mQzb</link>
      <guid>4M831MCuqbt45tWXa7mQzb</guid>
      <description>i feel like i owe you an update on my nicotine quitting journey. last time you heard, i had gotten through the first few weeks of painful withdrawal filled with anxiety, depression, sleepless nights, too much sleeping, intense cravings, mood swings, et cetera. and i had switched over from using a vape to using nicotine pouches. but i have a really disappointing update for you; it's going terrible. in fact, i have a vape in my pocket right now. i'm not proud to tell you this. i don't know if it's healthy to feel ashamed because i guess i'm doing my best to quit and inspire others to quit, but i'm not leading by example very well right now. but i want to tell you how this happened so that we can both learn from it.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>a spiritual awakening, a talk with lisa miller [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0kjO5cz6oLB4V0Ahdj2QA3</link>
      <guid>0kjO5cz6oLB4V0Ahdj2QA3</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] today i'm going to be speaking to dr. lisa miller. for so long, i've believed that spirituality and science cannot coexist. but what's so interesting about lisa to me is that she is a living example of the connection between spirituality and science. dr. lisa miller is the founder of spirituality mind body institute at columbia university. she's a professor of psychology, and has spent over a decade studying the impact of spirituality and religion on the brain. for those of you who are spiritual, this conversation with lisa is going to be like music to your ears. for those of you who are not spiritual, this might feel like a lot. but i encourage you to open your mind and heart, and let's get spiritual with lisa.find dr. miller's books on her website: www.lisamillerphd.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>only you know what's good for you [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6mLSDBQ6jEg5LpnAWawtWi</link>
      <guid>6mLSDBQ6jEg5LpnAWawtWi</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] my favorite type of content to consume online is content that tells me how to live my life. i've adopted so many habits and hobbies from other people that really inspire me. but this overexposure to different opinions and ways to live a good life can also be a bad thing. i think when it becomes a real problem is when we become obsessed with implementing a new habit or hobby into our lifestyle because it really worked for somebody else, but it's just not working for us. wasting our time trying to implement something into our lives that doesn't work prevents us from finding the things that do work. and i have a ton of examples to share of things that i tried to make fit for a little bit too long. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>what is &quot;good taste?&quot; [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3XdWhrSSQL63AUuQQylsfy</link>
      <guid>3XdWhrSSQL63AUuQQylsfy</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] what does it mean to have good taste in art, music, interior design, fashion, movies, photography? i almost get a gut reaction when i see something and decide whether or not i think it is a sign of good taste. but does it even exist, or is it too subjective? i'm not fully convinced that it doesn't exist, but we're going to go down the rabbit hole together and try to answer the question, what does it mean to have good taste? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>fashion identity crisis [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2SISVtTHnX6dvyhV4CqoEh</link>
      <guid>2SISVtTHnX6dvyhV4CqoEh</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] i had my first fashion identity crisis at the end of high school. that's when i started developing my personal style, and it took years to implement into my actual life. after my initial epiphany, i assumed that for the rest of my life I would have this sort of gradual evolution of my personal style. but apparently i was wrong because recently i found myself in another fashion identity crisis. and even if you're not somebody who uses fashion as a way to express yourself, you still will have periods in your life where you want to change your style too. so today i wanted to discuss how to change your style in a way that's efficient, smart, responsible, and effective. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>happiness is complicated [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1rKs96tNLrO4uDI5JcVg3z</link>
      <guid>1rKs96tNLrO4uDI5JcVg3z</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] when i was about 12 years old, i read a quote by john lennon that said “when i went to school, they asked me what i wanted to be when i grew up. i wrote down happy. they told me i didn't understand the assignment, and i told them they didn't understand life.” from that point forward, anytime anyone would ask me, emma, what do you wanna be when you grow up? i would answer happy. and so today i thought we would investigate happiness because it's a word that we use so often, but we rarely take a minute to step back and ask ourselves, what actually is this? how do we truly acquire this feeling? so let's investigate it together today. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;i don't chase i attract&quot; [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4FIK9leV1G5qX8CmkJTf6Y</link>
      <guid>4FIK9leV1G5qX8CmkJTf6Y</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] here i go again, analyzing another corny quote. on today's agenda, we have a quote that is beloved on social media right now: i don't chase, i attract. we all have a tendency to chase, especially in romantic relationships. i think the concept applies in career as well, but it really hits home for romantic relationships. so today i want to deep dive on this quote specifically within the context of romantic relationships, because i think that’s where it’s the most impactful. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>is romantic love an illusion? [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/566RRl5s2BioVXnliqdl8F</link>
      <guid>566RRl5s2BioVXnliqdl8F</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] is it just me, or is it starting to feel like romantic love is an illusion? i'm starting to question the concept of romantic love and what that experience is for us as humans because of my own life experiences, but also because the statistics are pretty damning. according to the american psychological association, approximately 40 to 50% of first marriages end in divorce. it's so fascinating to me that something so fundamental to human life seems destined to fail. as i'm maturing and facing these realities, i can't help but ask the question, why? and my brain immediately goes to, well, romantic love must just be an illusion. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>superstitions [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1auEzV2a5BvRXwsulV0F1r</link>
      <guid>1auEzV2a5BvRXwsulV0F1r</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] yesterday wasn't a great day for me. it all started when i showed up to my morning workout class and i realized that i had been booked on the 13th treadmill. i walked into the class and saw the treadmill with a big number 13 on it and i was like, this is bad luck. then on the way home, i saw a dead black cat on the side of the road. by then i was really freaking out because black cats are supposed to be bad luck and a dead black cat must be really bad luck. i was having all this anxiety about these bad omens, and i don't even know where i got those ideas from. do i even believe that those things are bad luck deeply to my core? no. but i realized yesterday that i am very superstitious and i hadn’t ever acknowledged it. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>hypnosis, a talk with ricky kalmon [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7HxNgj9PwoP07KRMATt847</link>
      <guid>7HxNgj9PwoP07KRMATt847</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] today i'm going to be speaking with ricky kalmon, a hypnotist. my curiosity around hypnosis has been growing recently because i've been going through this journey trying to quit nicotine, and one of the options I read about online to help me quit was hypnosis. i want to understand how and why it works, and honestly, what it even is in the first place. ricky is a hypnotist and a mindset expert. he speaks on how our mindset can be the greatest tool in achievement, reducing stress, and increasing productivity and potential. so i present to you, ricky kalmon. i can't wait. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>growing up too fast</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4LWfjSDLZItXBPEjSXwMtW</link>
      <guid>4LWfjSDLZItXBPEjSXwMtW</guid>
      <description>i had an epiphany recently that for my entire life thus far, i’ve been trying to grow up way too fast. in middle school and high school i wanted to find a boyfriend, have my first kiss, and lose my virginity. i wanted to do all of these things that i knew deep down i wasn't ready for, but my peers would praise me if i did. in my early twenties, i wanted to be more like a real adult: retire nightlife and start focusing on settling down and finding my future husband. but i had this sort of epiphany recently where i was like, hold on a minute. i'm 22 years old and I'm trying to live like 40 year old. why am i not giving myself the space and room to be young? so today we're going to be discussing the natural, self-inflicted desire to grow up too fast. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>comparison</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4JGniXPrmCEUqniY2k5YyQ</link>
      <guid>4JGniXPrmCEUqniY2k5YyQ</guid>
      <description>throughout my life, i've gone through phases of low self-esteem. this is normal, we all experience this. i'm not super excited to admit this, but for as long as i can remember, phases of low self-esteem have caused me to fixate on one person that i believe is better than me, and compare myself to them. their appearance, their relationship or lack thereof, their friend group, their job, their family situation… everything. i chose to admit this today because i'm talking about comparison. it’s a pretty normal human instinct, and it's important that we have the ability to compare, but when it comes to comparing ourselves, it gets a little bit more complicated. so let's figure out why we compare ourselves to others. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>am i burnt out or lazy? [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0NhqLlHSWcYi4IocMuSckb</link>
      <guid>0NhqLlHSWcYi4IocMuSckb</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] since high school, i've been cycling between two phases: wow, this girl is productive, and wow, this girl can't get anything done. when i'm in a productive phase, working comes easily to me. and when i'm in an unproductive phase, it's the complete opposite. during these unproductive times, i take a step back and analyze what's happening. and what i'm trying to figure out is am i being lazy, or am i burnt out? so today, i want to talk about the difference between laziness and burnout because they are kind of hard to distinguish, but understanding where you’re at helps you get back on track.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cultish, a talk with amanda montell [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7mpKt3Gz7XOZy5hdv6jgpK</link>
      <guid>7mpKt3Gz7XOZy5hdv6jgpK</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] today i present to you, amanda montell: a writer, linguist, and fellow podcast host. amanda has written three books. one of them, the age of magical overthinking, is about to come out. today i want to zoom in on one of our many common interests. she wrote an entire book about cults, the language used in cults, and cult-like behavior, and i'm excited to discuss how we participate in cult-like behavior on a day-to-day basis without even realizing it. she's really investigated the line between what is a cult and what is just cult-like behavior. and this is something I am curious to explore because I think it's a little bit more relevant than we even realize. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;you look tired... &quot; [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7L74lek8ykOaM9TtX2xTs6</link>
      <guid>7L74lek8ykOaM9TtX2xTs6</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] about a month ago, i posted a casual selfie, and i saw comments saying “wow, she looks tired,” and “she looks kind of sick.” i was like, wait a minute. i’m well rested and healthy… what's everyone going on about? and then it clicks. i'm not wearing makeup in that selfie. at first it was sort of disturbing to me that i was getting so many comments about how tired or sick i looked just because i wasn't wearing makeup. but then i had an epiphany. so that's what we're going to be talking about today: how makeup impacts the way that we perceive natural appearance.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>does everything happen for a reason? [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1QYqvOGAmIxdoDtiXE4Zev</link>
      <guid>1QYqvOGAmIxdoDtiXE4Zev</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] it's 2016. i'm 15 years old, and for the first time i'm realizing that life is challenging. i'm becoming obsessed with inspirational quotes. i think i’m having a philosophical awakening. now imagine during this time someone comes up to me and says, hey emma, what's your favorite quote? well, my answer would've been - everything happens for a reason. during that time, that quote answered all the questions that i needed answered, because my challenges were painfully simple. i thought i would get that tattooed on my body somewhere as a teenager, and i thank my lucky stars every day that i didn’t because i'll tell you, inspirational quotes look really good on the surface, but when you start to analyze them, they usually have some holes. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>unsolicited fashion advice</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7f40hHlGcl9y0RWEhMDv8M</link>
      <guid>7f40hHlGcl9y0RWEhMDv8M</guid>
      <description>unsolicited fashion advice Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>soulmates [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1XksrFB37u5dtIJwKQwiOA</link>
      <guid>1XksrFB37u5dtIJwKQwiOA</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] the concept of soulmates can be a relief to people, a nightmare, complete bullshit, or somewhere in between all of those things. everyone has their own unique perspective on the concept, and it's pretty rare to find two people who see it exactly the same. humanity as a whole has believed in soulmates for a very long time. though it's a very old concept, it has evolved to fit our current time. this isn't some sort of niche spiritual idea. this is very mainstream and even has sort of a trendy feel in some ways. so today we're going to talk about the concept of soulmates.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>great art takes time [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3F8zcZMJRQ1VSNBWtXFESi</link>
      <guid>3F8zcZMJRQ1VSNBWtXFESi</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] we're all constantly waiting on our favorite creatives to put out their next project. and the reason for that is because art takes a long time to create. i think a lot of us know this, but we forget this. i see a lot of fans online saying things to their favorite creatives like, hello, where's the next project? did you forget about us? are you being fucking lazy? it's very easy to believe that for artists, being creative is just automatic. and if they're not coming out with stuff left and right, it's because they don't want to. but that's very far from the truth. so today i want to talk about why good art takes time. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the challenges of running a business [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2hxthGrZvZo4A0vzkWXvwi</link>
      <guid>2hxthGrZvZo4A0vzkWXvwi</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] i rarely discuss the business side of my life. and i think that's for two reasons: number one, i fear it's boring, and number two, I feel like it doesn't align with how people see me. but today i'm finally going to let the business-minded side of myself speak. a few years ago i started my coffee company, chamberlain coffee. i had this rare opportunity to start a business with little to no experience because my career on the internet gave me the resources to reach out to people who knew how to make a business vision come to life. and throughout this experience, i've not only learned a lot, but have also grown an appreciation for the process itself. so today i'm going to list 10 of the challenges that i've faced running a business, and talk about what those 10 challenges taught me. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>quitting nicotine </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5Oy5bsziwrz6Tk81qdPsTi</link>
      <guid>5Oy5bsziwrz6Tk81qdPsTi</guid>
      <description>approximately three months ago i decided to embark on the journey to quit nicotine for good, and today's episode is going to be focusing on my experience thus far trying to quit. it's been incredibly hard. the reason why i feel the need to say how hard it is, is because people underestimate how severe nicotine addiction can be. i will say, it depends on the person and the level of addiction. but whether you or someone else in your life is addicted to nicotine and trying to quit, it's important to remember that it's not that easy. i was addicted to the vape specifically. that was my kryptonite. so with that in mind, i want to describe to you all of the different ways i’ve tried to get off the vape, and where i'm at in my process today. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>rejection [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2ysQGH2csDr1EDhdwvPknv</link>
      <guid>2ysQGH2csDr1EDhdwvPknv</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] today we're talking about being rejected. the thing about rejection is that we’ve all experienced it before, and we're all going to continue to experience rejection. it's just one of those things that we can't avoid. we can do everything right, and we're still at risk of being rejected. and i truly believe that when something's inevitable in life, it's much better to focus on finding a healthy way to handle it, than trying to avoid it at all costs. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice on taking advice [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2hOgcoWlc90uQsLCKejFeV</link>
      <guid>2hOgcoWlc90uQsLCKejFeV</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] we are all constantly receiving advice whether we asked for advice or not. we can receive advice from people that we know, like our family, friends, teachers, or bosses. we can also receive advice from less intimate sources, like random people on the internet, like me, or authors of books or writers of movies. we're constantly being thrown advice from all angles, and as a result, we're constantly sorting through advice deciding what the fuck to do with it. and a lot of that happens subconsciously because the giving and receiving of advice is such an automatic part of interacting as a human being. there are a lot of variables when it comes to this type of social interaction, but today i wanna zoom in on a specific type of advice interaction. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>would you rather: philosophical edition [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/14RYGMocWAcXqkbNpzF3DY</link>
      <guid>14RYGMocWAcXqkbNpzF3DY</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] i'm gonna be honest, i'm kind of falling apart over here. i lost my voice. i think it's because i've been singing in the car more than usual. i'm also on my period and i'm in a lot of pain. i'm really cramping up. yeah, i'm falling apart but i'm happy to be hanging out with you today, and turns out, despite all that i'm going through, i'm ready to use my brain. not my entire brain, but i'm in the mood to use seventy-five percent of my brain. i decided i wanted to play a little game of would you rather. a lot of times would you rather questions are like, “would you rather eat an eyeball or all of your fingernails?” that's fun, but i wanted to play would you rather in a way that really uses that seventy-five percent of my brain. so i went online and i found some vaguely philosophical would you rather questions. i think we're gonna have fun today. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>building a healthy social life [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/79Px58s1STer7yiJ4Rvghj</link>
      <guid>79Px58s1STer7yiJ4Rvghj</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] for the last few months, i've been on a journey. now that's not saying much because i'm always on some sort of journey. my particular journey as of recent has been rebuilding my social life. i didn't have a social life for a really long time because i didn't want one. for the past few years, all i've talked about is the importance of independence. but arriving to this point of independence, weirdly made me crave friendship. all of a sudden, after years of not really prioritizing friendship, my subconscious knew when i had arrived at a good place, that it was time to make friends again. it was like my subconscious told me, okay, it's time. it's time for you to go back out into the world and you need to put effort into your social life again.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>a clothing designer's mind, a talk with emily bode [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2nAT8TFRdqJWD91c5ianKB</link>
      <guid>2nAT8TFRdqJWD91c5ianKB</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] today i'm going to be interviewing one of my favorite, if not my favorite designers. she is the founder of her brand bode. maybe by definition bode is a men's wear brand, but bode is very much more than that. bode is a luxury brand with this sort of casual, vintage, eclectic edge. her brand is truly the epitome of vintage-inspired clothing, like she fucking nails it. bode makes it feel like you plucked it out of a store in the fifties. the brand really is helping to preserve the magical, beautiful craftsmanship of the past that's kind of slowly dwindling out of our day-to-day life. and bode is really one of one. i present to you emily adams bode aujla. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>trust your gut [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4TUM7gWyA2lsrJCrOyqEeU</link>
      <guid>4TUM7gWyA2lsrJCrOyqEeU</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] in life we're presented with a lot of questions that don't have concrete answers, and there are two ways that we can solve these problems. we can go with our gut instinct, which is our brain and body just automatically choosing the answer without thinking consciously. or we can come to a conclusion by really consciously analyzing the problem or question at hand; what are the pros and cons of taking each action, et cetera? i'm personally someone who tends to go with my intuition. that's not to say that i don't ever come to a conclusion based on heavy analysis, because i definitely do. but i would say four times out of five, i'm trusting my instincts. so what i'm here to talk about today is the value of your intuition.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>parasocial relationships [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/38xtpzbrqO1vK0CsHO3crx</link>
      <guid>38xtpzbrqO1vK0CsHO3crx</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] today we're going to be talking about us, because today's topic, parasocial relationships, addresses the type of relationship we have. parasocial relationships are one-sided relationships where one person extends emotional energy, interest and time, and the other party (the persona) is completely unaware of the other's existence. i've experienced both sides of a parasocial relationship, and as with all things, it can be a little toxic on both sides. but it can also be incredibly positive and healthy. i think my goal with this conversation is to just instill self-awareness and mindfulness around this topic so that both of us can have it in the back of our minds that we have to keep our parasocial relationships under control so that they can be a positive and healthy thing.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>what makes someone &quot;stylish?&quot; [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5roufAvFcIbTCPQLFyOz7N</link>
      <guid>5roufAvFcIbTCPQLFyOz7N</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] we all know stylish people, and it's easy to decide whether or not someone's stylish just by looking at them. it's pretty obvious. but it's much harder to describe what makes somebody stylish, or why somebody is stylish. so today i want to discuss what truly makes someone stylish. but here's something i want to discuss before we even get into it; not everybody wants to be stylish or looks at clothes as a way to express themselves. and that's okay too. but if you're into fashion and expressing yourself in that way, it can be an incredible hobby. but it’s just not mandatory, and it's not for everyone. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>modern romance, a talk with lori gottlieb [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7CWLvd03PyEAespcOUpMpp</link>
      <guid>7CWLvd03PyEAespcOUpMpp</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] today we're going to be talking to dr. lori gottlieb. she’s a psychotherapist, author of the new york times bestselling book “maybe you should talk to someone,” and co-host of the “dear therapists” podcast. she’s an expert on all things therapy, mental health, psychology, you name it. i wanna specifically talk to her about romantic relationships. there's a lot of challenges that come with dating in the age of technology, and i'm curious to talk to a psychotherapist about the challenges of dating in our modern world, while also just talking about relationships in general. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>when toxic becomes trendy [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2ud2UZt14Bow19KsrxBamB</link>
      <guid>2ud2UZt14Bow19KsrxBamB</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] i have a feeling that the parents are gonna love this episode. certain topics just make me fall into mom mode, where all of a sudden i'm saying that the internet is poison and that marijuana is the devil's lettuce. i'll tell you to go outside and touch grass, and i have a feeling that today's topic will send me straight into mom mode. i've recently noticed quite a few trends online that are really toxic and really unhealthy and really bad for society overall, in my opinion. and they've just been sitting in my mind, rotting, growing mold, growing fungus, and i just wanna discuss them today. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;happiness is only real when shared&quot; [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4WjHu1hLwDFw2PzaV2SoaS</link>
      <guid>4WjHu1hLwDFw2PzaV2SoaS</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] recently i watched a movie that was pretty good, and one of the last scenes provided a quote that has been stuck in my brain ever since. the main character writes down in the margins of a book, “happiness is only real when shared.” now i rarely see a quote and think to myself, i've actually never thought that before. but this quote blew my mind. i know we're gonna be fighting against cringe this whole episode because it is a little corny to talk about a quote to the length that i'm about to talk about a quote. but there's just so much truth here and unfortunately for you, i just have to. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>running away from problems [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4iIG7OZ1bcvXLUSxm9yB3e</link>
      <guid>4iIG7OZ1bcvXLUSxm9yB3e</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] about two months ago i was kind of going through it, and around that time i had a trip coming up. without realizing, i sort of put off dealing with the challenges that i was being faced with in my life. subconsciously i thought this trip was going to just erase my problems. and i very quickly realized that problems follow you everywhere. i was on this trip dealing with all these unresolved issues because simply being in another country wasn't going to fix anything. reality hit me hard, and there was no ignoring it. this experience made me hyper aware of how damaging it can be to run away from your problems. so, all that to say, today we're gonna be discussing running away from our problems. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>what history can teach us, a talk with michael bess [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2kZBpUURUaLfODFQ425XQa</link>
      <guid>2kZBpUURUaLfODFQ425XQa</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] today we're going to be talking to michael bess. michael bess is chancellor's professor of history at vanderbilt university, where he has been teaching for the past 34 years. he's the author of five books, and a specialist in 20th and 21st century europe with a particular interest in the interactions between social and cultural processes and technological change. today i want to discuss with him how technology has impacted our quality of life over the past few centuries. i also want to discuss the ways that we might romanticize the past. and last but not least, i want to discuss how the internet impacts our perception of our current times, and how that's possibly very damaging. just sit back, relax, and enjoy my conversation with the incredible michael bess. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>embarrassing things i did in high school [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/26QK7E8fsiWqKmozpARdYy</link>
      <guid>26QK7E8fsiWqKmozpARdYy</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] i think i'm finally at a place now where i can look back at my high school memories and i can laugh. and it's such a relief because prior to now, anytime i'd remember an embarrassing high school memory, it was still too cringe to me. but i'm finally at a place now where i think i'm ready to share some of these memories, and what a beautiful thing that is. because cringey moments can haunt you. but eventually you get to a point where they become fun, funny, and somewhat a source of joy. so all of that to say, today i'm going to be telling some of my embarrassing high school stories. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>procrastination [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1FUdCAS2vNpeftPCDxCwhn</link>
      <guid>1FUdCAS2vNpeftPCDxCwhn</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] i got the idea for this episode because i was quite literally procrastinating writing an outline for a podcast episode. i didn't have an idea for a topic, or the mental energy to sit down and brainstorm. and i realized, everyone struggles with this. at times the human condition can feel like this constant fight against procrastination. we always have things that we need to do, and simultaneously we have so many things that we'd rather be doing that are more fun, lighthearted, and enjoyable. and the thing about procrastination is that not only does it cause stress, but it can also impact our self-esteem. it’s something that a lot of us only vaguely understand. we know we do it, but we don't fully understand why we do it or how we can stop doing it. so let’s talk about it. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nicotine addiction</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3zMljWPy6PGukbVjkWl5aO</link>
      <guid>3zMljWPy6PGukbVjkWl5aO</guid>
      <description>this is a topic that i have avoided forever, because i never wanted to have to admit to my own addiction publicly. but here i am today admitting to you that i have a very severe nicotine addiction. not a day has gone by in the last five years where i haven't consumed nicotine in some form. but recently, i decided that i want to try to quit. and because i'm at a place in my life where i'm trying to quit, i feel morally okay about discussing the topic. i was never proud of my nicotine addiction. in fact, i was always kind of ashamed of it. but two weeks ago, i decided i was done. and now this is a topic i feel comfortable discussing. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>self-discipline [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2TN40JPlyzTRLr78O6Dlpz</link>
      <guid>2TN40JPlyzTRLr78O6Dlpz</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] when i sit and analyze the most fulfilling times of my life, i notice a lot of patterns. one thing that stands out is thatduring fulfilling times, i tend to have a healthy amount of self-discipline that helps create stability and joy in my life. in my own words, i think having discipline is striving towards an ultimate goal that feels worthy to you, and striving to be the best person you can be. but if discipline were as easy to master as just forcing yourself to do what's right and forcing yourself to take the steps to reach your ultimate goal, then we would have nothing more to talk about. discipline is complicated because not only is it challenging to cultivate in the first place, but just as much as we need to have discipline, we also need to treat ourselves gently and with compassion. and finding that balance is a challenge in and of itself. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>a talk with owen thiele [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5B8eRvOldnewb1R8agkrBF</link>
      <guid>5B8eRvOldnewb1R8agkrBF</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] today we're going to be talking to one of my best friends, owen thiele. i am so excited to be interviewing a friend today because i just think it's gonna be a total hoot. owen and i have a lot in common: we're both only children, we have anxiety about the same things, we tend to like the same people… i absolutely adore him. owen is an incredible comedian and an incredible actor, and if you want to see owen in a movie, mark your calendar for july 14th and go see theater camp. okay, now we can welcome owen thiele to the stage. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>things i like rn [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1CpnL0smn8EDiaR4W3y9LB</link>
      <guid>1CpnL0smn8EDiaR4W3y9LB</guid>
      <description>[video available on spotify] when i woke up this morning, i decided i'm not going to think very hard today. i opened my eyes and said, today's going to be a simple day. so in honor of that, i decided i'd share with you some simple things that i like a lot. that's it. just some things that are bringing me joy in this current moment. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>what makes art good?</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3d13yPhoOAOej3lPXZg3oJ</link>
      <guid>3d13yPhoOAOej3lPXZg3oJ</guid>
      <description>when i experience art, i can almost immediately determine whether or not i think it's good. but i rarely ask myself why it's good. and recently i decided to do that. what's complicated about art is that it’s subjective, and everybody connects to art differently. so good art to one person is bad art to the next person. but i do think that there is an answer to the question, what is good art? so that's what we're going to discuss today. and listen, a conversation about art can very quickly turn pretentious and cringe. but i am going to do everything in my power today to make this not pretentious and cringe.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>what if you are the problem? [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6CJzBRgTQvYbWKHAjaedxs</link>
      <guid>6CJzBRgTQvYbWKHAjaedxs</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] i feel like the automatic response to a problem or conflict is to blame everyone and everything other than ourselves. it's not very automatic to run into a problem and immediately ask, did this problem arise or did this conflict happen because i did something wrong? for the last two years, i've been working on asking myself if there’s any chance that maybe i'm the problem, and reflecting on whether or not i actually did do something wrong when conflict arises. it’s a lot easier to start pointing fingers and blaming everything on everyone else. it makes us feel like we're in the power position. it allows us to play the victim in a way, which can be a much more comfortable place to be. but i truly believe that life gets better when we get into the habit of asking ourselves if we are the problem. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“romanticizing” your life</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2sVSi2JAWvATej2pXgv28h</link>
      <guid>2sVSi2JAWvATej2pXgv28h</guid>
      <description>to romanticize is by definition to deal with or describe in an idealized or unrealistic fashion; to make something seem better or more appealing than it really is. today we're talking about making a deliberate, conscious choice to romanticize life. romanticizing life became sort of a social media trend about turning mundane daily moments into magical moments. i think a lot of us feel really disconnected from the simple pleasures of life due to the sort of fast-paced, highly technological reality we live in today. we get into a routine, and certain daily activities and tasks turn into meaningless chunks of our day. romanticizing life won’t solve all of your problems, but i think this philosophy paired with a level of mindfulness and awareness can help those mundane moments in life become a lot more enjoyable. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>underrated fashion trends [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1i2dk8adGOi3mvtaVVdlRy</link>
      <guid>1i2dk8adGOi3mvtaVVdlRy</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] today i'm going to be discussing some fashion trends that i believe are underrated. it's not that these fashion trends never get worn and never get discussed, but in my opinion, they don't get enough airtime. so today i'm going to sit here and give them the airtime that they deserve. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>a talk with mac demarco [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7tAk82Jr3FQ8rqHyzGGm77</link>
      <guid>7tAk82Jr3FQ8rqHyzGGm77</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] today i have a very special guest. someone who actually shifted my music taste in a big way. today we have mac demarco. when i was like 15 i found his music on vine, and i've been such a big fan ever since. i think what's so special about mac’s music is the way it always sounds like him. whether it's kind of funky, deep and sentimental, or just an instrumental, it always feels like him. his last album having almost 200 songs and being like nine hours long is so intriguing to me. he's going the complete opposite direction of the industry, and i must know more. so i present to you, mac demarco. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>a message from emma [video trailer]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4nqzojtIAYL2UmNvmvs8Z6</link>
      <guid>4nqzojtIAYL2UmNvmvs8Z6</guid>
      <description>on june 8, big things are happening on anything goes! it's the podcast you know and love, now with the occasional special guest video interview. emma will sit down with anyone from experts to music artists, so stay tuned because anything goes. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>are you living for you? [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3Rv8iiTbchvpmF9B8pdBvm</link>
      <guid>3Rv8iiTbchvpmF9B8pdBvm</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] there have been many times in my life where i've found myself feeling really unhappy and not knowing what the issue was. and i've often realized that in those moments, i was feeling unhappy because i was not living life for me. i was living life for everyone and everything else. i wasn't listening to my own opinions. i wasn't making decisions for me. and what's really interesting about falling into a phase like this is that you don't always notice it. it happens slowly and is not obvious. and so today i want to talk about living life for you. i want to discuss some of the sneaky ways that you can find yourself in a routine where you're not living for you, discuss what it can look like, and how to get out of it. because when you're living life truly for you, it's so freeing. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>disliking people</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1uSHGrPiuxxcyegxuZw4WL</link>
      <guid>1uSHGrPiuxxcyegxuZw4WL</guid>
      <description>when i think about it, i actually dislike a lot of people. i wouldn't say i hate a lot of people, but i definitely dislike a lot of people. now, to me, there's a big difference between dislike and hate. for the sake of today's conversation, let's look at dislike as a subtle feeling that can be much more easily controlled. i've found myself wondering recently if i'm the problem. is it wrong to dislike people? i never act upon my dislike. i never treat people that i don't like badly. i keep most of those feelings inside. so in theory, it's kind of harmless because the people that we dislike often don't really know that we dislike them. but i still feel sort of guilty about it. so let’s get into it. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>outfit repeating [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3XTQ5AFQUtQ5dClsYvr9Qy</link>
      <guid>3XTQ5AFQUtQ5dClsYvr9Qy</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] i think all of us can look at the concept of outfit repeating and say, why is this even a topic of conversation? but what's wild to me is how common it is for people to be concerned about repeating the same outfit more than once. not only have i experienced this pressure to not repeat outfits, but i've also seen it in the world. when you go through any influencer's page on instagram, you will probably not see them wear the same thing twice. and then there are lots of people who can't be concerned with the concept of outfit repeating because they don't have that luxury. outfit repeating is absolutely a luxury. and i sort of don't even want to talk about it because by talking about it, i'm giving it more legitimacy than it deserves. but at the same time, i do want to discuss it because i think it's something a lot of people experience, whether they're fortunate enough to actually take it seriously as a concern, or if they wish that they could think of it as a concern. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the ethics of facetune [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2yelIHgbV6PjWtpGNBFZHz</link>
      <guid>2yelIHgbV6PjWtpGNBFZHz</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] today i want to discuss the ethics of photo editing on social media. i'm not talking about upping the brightness or turning down the contrast on the photo a little bit. i'm talking about going in and changing the image completely. smoothing out your skin, making your waist a little smaller or your jaw line a little sharper. you used to have to know how to use professional photo editing software like photoshop to edit photos, and it wasn’t easy. but photo editing apps are incredibly accessible now and easy to use. it's so tempting to want to go in and tweak little things about an image so that you love it. and i think the most dangerous part about photo editing these days is that it can be impossible to spot. social media in general has had catastrophic effects on people's mental health, and that's ignoring the retouching side of things. so i'm facing a sort of moral dilemma. what I'm trying to figure out is, is it ever okay to alter your appearance in imagery? because when i look at this dilemma at face value, i think we should probably avoid this at all costs. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>living in fear [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4K7DhGh2h6b16KavahbBj0</link>
      <guid>4K7DhGh2h6b16KavahbBj0</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] i recently found myself in an unusual state of terror and fear. i've always been very afraid of bad things happening to my loved ones. but weirdly, i've never really been that afraid of bad things happening to me. in retrospect, i look at the things that i used to do when i was a teenager that were sort of careless, and it's hard for me to even comprehend now. i felt like nothing bad would happen to me. but recently, i have completely gone the opposite direction, where now i'm terrified of the world around me and how it might hurt me. and that's not healthy either, because when you're living in that state of mind, you sort of stop living your life. there's risk in everything. and you have to have a healthy understanding of what risks are worth taking and which are not. and i've sort of gone on this journey the last few months trying to find a healthy and happy medium. i'm not 100% there yet, but i'm getting much closer. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the age of indulgence, a talk with dr. lembke [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2XAnegrxPjwfFu7UaOt3dg</link>
      <guid>2XAnegrxPjwfFu7UaOt3dg</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] today i'm doing my very first interview. we're getting into serious podcast territory. i'm bringing dr. lembke on the show today because i've been obsessed with the sneaky addictions of our modern day. you know, the addictions that our grandparents and parents are warning us about: social media, food delivery, porn, gaming… all of the addictions that we're sort of in denial of. she describes the time that we're living in now as the age of indulgence, and i've never heard this time be characterized better. it really is this age of indulgence where everything is at our fingertips, and at face value it seems incredible. but there are a lot of scary downsides. i'm going to be discussing all of this and more with dr. lembke.link to dr. lembke’s book, dopamine nation: https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/624957/dopamine-nation-by-anna-lembke-md/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i tried a dopamine “detox”</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4SDT2cGvPHN4SokoLU7ru3</link>
      <guid>4SDT2cGvPHN4SokoLU7ru3</guid>
      <description>about a week ago, i had the realization that i had fallen into some bad habits. i'd been scrolling on social media a little bit too much, online shopping a little bit too much, ordering food delivery a little bit too much, and more. my brain felt cloudy. i felt anxious. i felt kind of depressed. i didn't feel as creative or as focused as i knew i could be. and i really make an effort in my life to have a healthy balance with modern convenience and entertainment, because i know how addictive these things are and how toxic they can be. but when i had this realization a week ago, i had the desire to take drastic measures. i decided i was going to do a dopamine detox. if you haven't heard of a dopamine detox, i'll explain it. and i will say this challenge, as minor as it may seem, was really eye-opening for me. it was challenging, but it was very rewarding. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>minimalism (part 3: fashion)</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5kw0H4YrS49BjGIazBulKN</link>
      <guid>5kw0H4YrS49BjGIazBulKN</guid>
      <description>today we're going to be discussing minimalism in fashion. fast fashion is the business model of replicating recent high fashion design trends, mass producing them at low cost, and bringing them to retail stores quickly while demand is at its highest. trend cycles are insanely fast nowadays, and fast fashion is thriving because a lot of people want to participate in the trends as they happen. but i think a lot of people are sick of this. number one, it's exhausting and expensive to keep up with all the trends when they're constantly changing overnight. but also, people are starting to realize the impact that being a maximalist consumer is having on the environment and even their wellbeing. i think a lot of people are ready to dial it back and return to a simpler fashion experience. so let's dig a little deeper on what minimalism is in fashion. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>minimalism (part 2: travel)</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5hFTxPgFUycyIP6i8VyRW8</link>
      <guid>5hFTxPgFUycyIP6i8VyRW8</guid>
      <description>last summer, my dad and i spent a month in europe. and before we left for our trip, my dad said, i challenge you to fit everything you need for a month in europe in a carry-on suitcase. at first i was like, there's no way. some people would call me an over packer. but even when i over-pack, i still end up wearing the same outfit the entire trip and half of my suitcase remains untouched. so last summer when my dad said, i dare you to fit everything into a carry-on suitcase, i was unsure because i was so used to the ease of having everything and more that i could possibly need in my suitcase. a month is a long time and a carry-on is small. but although it was challenging, i enjoyed it immensely. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>minimalism (part 1: lifestyle)</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5DViRaUMyDnUYgKWkPcBc2</link>
      <guid>5DViRaUMyDnUYgKWkPcBc2</guid>
      <description>over the past few years, we've experienced a lot of maximalism across the board. it's been a major lifestyle trend. it's been a major fashion trend. it's been a present theme over the past few years. but i feel like its trendiness might be coming to a temporary end. maybe it's just me, but i've been feeling this collective fatigue. we're sick of it, we're tired of it, we're ready to go back to minimalism. and so i present to you part one of a three part series on minimalism. today in part one, we're going to be discussing the minimalist lifestyle. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>lower your expectations about people [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7DKl2PWdh0z1Y7e40R5rEH</link>
      <guid>7DKl2PWdh0z1Y7e40R5rEH</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] we often find ourselves disappointed with other people. there are times when we set realistic expectations for people, such as expecting somebody to treat you with respect, or to follow the law and not steal from you or harm you. those are realistic, normal, healthy expectations to have. but there are times when we become disappointed in people because they didn't meet our expectations. but we have to ask ourselves, did we set the expectation too high? today i want to talk about having unrealistic expectations about people and why we should try to eradicate those from our mind. because i think many of us expect a lot. and it's complicated because having a set of expectations for how you want to be treated and for who you want to have in your life is important, healthy, and how you keep yourself safe and happy. but at the same time, we can take it too far and we can set expectations for people that are impossible to reach. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>is marriage outdated? [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3LjYQfdVLR6LWPU6NWaWPM</link>
      <guid>3LjYQfdVLR6LWPU6NWaWPM</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] today i'm going to be talking about a topic that is not a hot topic: marriage. when my parents were growing up, marriage was this sort of fundamental part of being a human. and recent statistics are showing that millennials and gen z are apparently not loving the idea of getting married. when i was younger i really didn't know if i wanted to get married and have kids. part of it could have been that my parents were divorced. but I think a big part of why i had that belief was out of this desire to rebel against the norm. it's fascinating to me that something so foundational like marriage is being so heavily questioned. it's making me wonder whether or not the questioning is rational, or if it's just kind of an act of rebellion against society. because when we're told to do something, sometimes we freak out and decide to rebel against it. so i guess i just want to investigate all of it. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>coachella fashion analysis [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/18NEMdPnbYfdgIgBFCbOfC</link>
      <guid>18NEMdPnbYfdgIgBFCbOfC</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] guess who just got back from coachella? me. if you don't know what coachella is, it’s one of the biggest music festivals in America, where the biggest musicians perform all in one place. there are celebrities everywhere, all doing things that warrant headlines. it's just one of those things that i refuse to miss every year. but today i specifically want to talk about coachella fashion because although music is the number one priority, fashion is a close second. it's undeniably a fashion moment that is recognized by even the largest fashion magazines and brands. and the interesting thing about coachella is that there's sort of no dress code. i think the only rule is you can't be completely nude, but you can be really close and you can still get in. and i feel like this lack of dress code combined with this mass of people all in one place makes it the perfect moment to express yourself with clothing in a really unique way. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>is it narcissistic to post photos of yourself? [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/67HQt7ICKI3ufq02bFi8oY</link>
      <guid>67HQt7ICKI3ufq02bFi8oY</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] recently, i've felt weird posting pictures of myself on instagram, and i've never felt this feeling before. posting photos of ourselves online is a part of being human at this point. it's so incredibly normal. i think most of us aren't even questioning why we do it. and up until recently, i didn't question it either. but the last few times I've gone to post a photo of myself on instagram, i've felt like a narcissist, and it scared me a little bit. i've been finding myself taking a pause before i post a picture of myself feeling almost uncertain of whether or not it's the right thing to do. and i'm somebody who has a tendency to overthink, so part of me wonders if i'm overthinking the whole thing. but part of me also thinks there's a chance that even though we've normalized posting photos of ourselves, it's still actually a narcissistic behavior. so today, I wanna figure out for myself honestly, whether or not posting photos of yourself online is narcissistic.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>why do famous people choose to stay famous? [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2edRt35hjXV2kmCoY65ddq</link>
      <guid>2edRt35hjXV2kmCoY65ddq</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] why do celebrities choose to stay famous? on the surface level, this question seems easy to answer because most of us look at fame as a dream come true. we see fortune, power, attention, praise. we see all of the positives. but yet, right in front of our eyes, we witness the way that fame ruins people's lives. it's safe to say that fame is much more complicated than we think it is on the surface level. as much as there are incredible elements of being famous that are life-changing and full of abundance, there are also sides of it that are so challenging that even all the money and abundance in the world can't heal those wounds at times. and so today i wanna try to answer the question, why do famous people stay famous? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the fear of missing out [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/54nuvDsSeAXftXxDv1U0BA</link>
      <guid>54nuvDsSeAXftXxDv1U0BA</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] i had fomo recently. what is fomo? fomo is the fear of missing out. it's probably not an unfamiliar feeling to you as i assume most people feel fomo at least once in their life. the more expanded definition of fomo is anxiety that an exciting or interesting event may currently be happening elsewhere, often aroused by posts seen on social media. i thought that i was done experiencing fomo. i thought i grew out of fomo. i thought i had evolved past the point of experiencing that feeling, but i was wrong.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>karma [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3teuBkAn6Vpm0PJnkUXqdA</link>
      <guid>3teuBkAn6Vpm0PJnkUXqdA</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] ever since i discovered the concept of karma, i’ve been obsessed with it. i learned it through my community. it might have been my parents, it might have been my friends, it might have been my teachers, i don't remember. but the moral of the story is ever since i've discovered karma, i have been obsessed with the concept. i’ve been living with karma in mind for pretty much as long as I can remember, and it's been a fundamental rule in my life. but as i'm getting older, i'm becoming more fascinated by these rules that i've been living by. i'm questioning them in a way, but not necessarily in a negative way or even in a super critical way. moreso wondering what more is there to learn about these certain concepts and how accurate are they? i just find the whole thing interesting and satisfying. so today we're gonna be digging into karma. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>it feels like everyone has a podcast these days [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0s0DCUsNCgXQSl3FfsJmfP</link>
      <guid>0s0DCUsNCgXQSl3FfsJmfP</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] have you been thinking to yourself, everybody has a podcast these days? i think a lot of people are feeling that way. over the past few years, podcasting has become a real thing. when I was younger, the only podcasts i knew of were ones that were for adults that my parents were listening to. they were all very corporate in the sense that they weren't just individuals turning on a microphone and making a podcast kind of indie style. i don't remember podcasting being a thing for anyone under 40 up until the last maybe five years. but it's definitely become a huge source of entertainment for all ages. and I just wanted to analyze this today because I'm so fascinated by the podcasting world and how it's grown over the past few years, and especially how it's entered into the universe of young people. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the obsession with having an &quot;aesthetic” [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0GgJWO8hQMq1F6V6qaywpC</link>
      <guid>0GgJWO8hQMq1F6V6qaywpC</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] today i’m going to be talking about something that i'm obsessed with. in 2023, our identities as human beings are not just confined to our physical being. our identities are now a combination of our online presence and our physical presence. prior to the internet, if you weren't a celebrity, your entire identity was judged based on your physical presence. at this point in time, your online identity and your physical presence equally, in my opinion, shape the way that people perceive you. i've noticed that with the rapid development of social media, there has also been a rapid development of different aesthetics that people align themselves with in a way that goes beyond just lighthearted interests. to me, it feels like people's online aesthetics become almost a lifestyle, almost an obsession, almost a religion in some cases, and this is so fascinating to me. so today we're talking about our collective obsession with having an aesthetic, especially online. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>character assassination</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0FcVazVpEwv5AaVQIQoLtQ</link>
      <guid>0FcVazVpEwv5AaVQIQoLtQ</guid>
      <description>i've had character assassination on my list of topics for weeks now, because it didn't feel particularly relevant to my life. but the topic became incredibly relevant to my personal life recently, so here we are. character assassination is the malicious and unjustified harming of a person's good reputation. i think it can come in two main forms. number one, a completely fabricated story that doesn't have an ounce of truth in it, that's created simply to harm someone's reputation. and then the second type is a dramatized negative version of the truth. so this is taking a little piece of truth and twisting it into something that is far more negative and defamatory than it actually is. this has always been an issue for public figures and celebrities. character assassination sells. but i would say prior to the internet, there was no way for the average person to just go viral on a whim like it's possible now. the moral of the story is anyone now can be the victim of public shaming and public character assassination at an astronomically larger scale than necessary. and before we go any further, i'd like to tell my story of my own character sort of being assassinated recently. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>how i deal with dissociating and anxiety [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/74DfAhaU9bz2F94JJzY1PD</link>
      <guid>74DfAhaU9bz2F94JJzY1PD</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] today i wanted to talk about something super fun, super lighthearted, super hashtag good vibes. that's just the mood I'm in today. so today i wanted to talk about my anxiety. yayyyyyyy. i wanted to talk about it because it's one of the most challenging things i deal with on a daily basis. i’ve struggled with a lot of different mental health struggles. anxiety is definitely not the only one. but i would say anxiety has been the most challenging overall, and it just never really seems to go away for me. it's something that i'm constantly battling, and so i just wanted to talk about my experience and how i deal with it. and that's what's on the agenda. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the mental health conversation on the internet [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5xlrjZOuhgHqBF3sSjRazq</link>
      <guid>5xlrjZOuhgHqBF3sSjRazq</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] i’ve been talking openly about my mental health on the internet for years now. i think it’s just who i am by nature. i’ve never had much of an issue talking about my struggles, and i think the conversation about mental health is an incredible thing. but the fact that i’m involved in the conversation online about mental health has made me hyper aware of the conversation itself, and has caused me to analyze it as a whole. what are people saying online in regards to mental health? what advice and knowledge are people sharing? two things can be true at once - something can be incredible, and helpful, and lifesaving, and it can also be incredibly damaging, misguided and harmful. and i think that’s happening with this mental health conversation online. it’s an important conversation to have. so today we’re going to talk about the evolution of the mental health conversation online, the benefits of it, and the negative impacts of this conversation.this episode contains some very heavy topics. we talk about suicide, eating disorders, and other mental health issues. so if you think this will be upsetting for you, please don't listen to this episode. for resources on these topics, visit spotify.com/resources.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>my daily routine, explained [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4MWuN0RGpVD1ons5xu3AIT</link>
      <guid>4MWuN0RGpVD1ons5xu3AIT</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] today i wanted to walk you through my daily routine. i’m talking about from the second i wake up, to the second i go to sleep. i want to explain why i do the things i do, why i find them beneficial, and just get into the nitty gritty of my daily routine. because i feel like i have a really solid daily routine at this point. so i wanted to dig into it. talk about it, analyze it, discuss it.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>social life, success, and sleep [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6i37m4hQjSz4MpohR7gk1i</link>
      <guid>6i37m4hQjSz4MpohR7gk1i</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] when i was in high school i was scrolling through instagram, and i stumbled upon a graphic of a triangle. at the end of each tip of the triangle there was a priority - sleep, success in work/school, and social life. on the bottom of the screen it said choose two. the concept was that you can’t prioritize everything in your life at the same time. for years of my life i’ve sort of lived with this instagram graphic in the back of my head. i’ve constantly reminded myself, something’s gotta give. i can’t prioritize everything i want to prioritize 100%. but recently i had an epiphany and thought, is this true? so today i want to explore this concept, because i think there’s a lot of value there, but it could use a little bit more nuance.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>trendy or timeless #3 [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1qNJ1bZ27KxcD0VNhFxwrU</link>
      <guid>1qNJ1bZ27KxcD0VNhFxwrU</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] today we’re going to be doing another episode of trendy or timeless. this is when i look at fashion trends that are hot right now and discuss whether i think they’re trendy or timeless, and just what i think of them overall. so let’s get right into it.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>we know nothing [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0fJ1r1F8StQ8ER5d8u6ki8</link>
      <guid>0fJ1r1F8StQ8ER5d8u6ki8</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] today we’re going to be talking about how we don’t know shiiittttt. listen, it’s very easy to fall into a cycle where you believe that you know everything: that you’re right, that you have shit figured out, and that everyone else who disagrees with you is a dummy. now, i know not everybody’s like this. you may not be like this. but at the very least, you definitely know someone like this… a know-it-all. but a discovery i’ve made in my adult life is that it’s such a beautiful and magical thing to realize that you know nothing. it’s so freeing. and that’s why i wanted to talk about it today. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>weird stuff i've bought recently [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1lCz2mvTTLViTrcfLVOcFt</link>
      <guid>1lCz2mvTTLViTrcfLVOcFt</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] today i'm going to be talking about some of the unnecessary things i've bought recently, and whether or not i think they’re worth the money. these are things that aren't necessary but are extremely helpful. that’s like my shopping kryptonite. if something is not necessary but extremely helpful, unfortunately i have to have it. i’m not proud of it necessarily, but i'm going to share some of my discoveries with you. not all of these things were hits, okay, some of these were terrible and we’re going to talk about that too. but listen, some of these things were great so i'm going to put you on. and for the things that are bad, now you know not to waste your time. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>is creativity dead? [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/62eUfCvGhZvz8HQwwuCZTj</link>
      <guid>62eUfCvGhZvz8HQwwuCZTj</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] i’ve been asking myself for a long time, have all creative things been done before? has every piece of clothing been created? has every movie been made? has every song been written? humans have been expressing themselves creatively for thousands of years and part of me is starting to wonder if we’ve hit our limit. have we created everything that’s possible to be created? i know for a fact there are incredible creatives today, but as a whole, it seems like a lot of what’s being produced on a mainstream level is not up to the standard that mainstream creativity used to meet. now, I also need to mention that everything i’m about to say could be complete bullshit. When in doubt, remember that everything i say is a hypothesis and i’m so open to other opinions and people telling me i'm wrong. let’s get into it. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>my hair fell out [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5n4dx3SvRUVEtrNrNiNWSB</link>
      <guid>5n4dx3SvRUVEtrNrNiNWSB</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] i have a horror story for you. an absolute horror story. it has to do with my hair. so let’s just get into it, let’s waste no time. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>do we need religion? [video]</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6HomB4XtrLkC5EVRTMtl6i</link>
      <guid>6HomB4XtrLkC5EVRTMtl6i</guid>
      <description>[video available on Spotify] today i want to talk about religion. what a fun topic. i’ve been thinking about religion a lot recently, not on a personal level, but on a societal level. i want to start by saying i have no bias. i have my own spiritual beliefs that keep me afloat, but i’m not married to a religion. i also have to mention that this conversation is based on my corner of the internet, my corner of the world, and what i’m seeing. depending on where you live or what communities you’re a part of, you might have a very different experience. so i ask you to keep that in mind. let’s get into it. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>analyzing couple behavior</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1KMMRBDOI9qz7XkHym7aO2</link>
      <guid>1KMMRBDOI9qz7XkHym7aO2</guid>
      <description>you know what i love to do? analyze people. and you know what my favorite dynamic to analyze is? romantic relationships. i think it’s because romantic relationships are possibly the most vulnerable relationship. they bring out every side of a person. they show every weakness, every strength, every flaw… they show traits of a person that might otherwise just sit underneath the surface. so today i wanted to discuss some behaviors that i’ve observed in other peoples relationships, and maybe even some of my own past relationships as well. and i want to talk about what i think these behaviors mean. i must say, these are all just hypotheses. none of it’s backed by science, it’s just backed by life experience. let’s just get into it.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>past, present, future</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2xOBZ5aWSsHCSANYU1acj1</link>
      <guid>2xOBZ5aWSsHCSANYU1acj1</guid>
      <description>today i wanted to talk about how we view the past, the present, and the future. i’ve had healthy and unhealthy relationships with these three time periods throughout my life, and i can almost guarantee that you have too. it’s easy to become obsessed with the past, or the present, or the future in a way that’s imbalanced. so today i wanted to talk about what i think are healthy perceptions of these time periods, and what might be unhealthy. let’s get into it. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>realistic habits</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6gFiu9yBlbSjdDjsBJf8V4</link>
      <guid>6gFiu9yBlbSjdDjsBJf8V4</guid>
      <description>don’t you just love it when you’re scrolling through social media, and you stumble upon a little video of somebody showing their daily routine? they wake up at 5AM, roll out of their crisp white sheets, take a shower, do a 40 step skincare routine and give themselves a full blowout so that their hair is perfect and wavy and gorgeous... you get what i’m saying. we all talk about how social media is not real life these days, but even i get swept up into the world of the internet sometimes. i watch a video of somebody's perfect daily routine and i don’t feel good, because i’m like, i’ll never be like that. but the truth is, the whole thing is unrealistic! i think that the pressure to have your shit together is a little bit unhealthy, and there’s an obsession with it on the internet. so that’s what i want to talk about today. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>anything goes comes to spotify - trailer</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2iMzFtiH7BQvvstzMWKxHB</link>
      <guid>2iMzFtiH7BQvvstzMWKxHB</guid>
      <description>starting thursday, february 23rd, emma chamberlain's podcast anything goes will be exclusive on spotify. it's the same podcast you know and love, but with the occasional addition of extras - including guests and video episodes. stay tuned, because anything goes. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the rules we learned as kids... are BS?</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/76Rn9J0d9DFUSEh4JbMy1l</link>
      <guid>76Rn9J0d9DFUSEh4JbMy1l</guid>
      <description>remember when you were a child and constantly had adults telling you what the rules were? don’t lie, don’t steal... don’t do this, don’t do that. when we’re children, we’re constantly being reminded of certain rules and principles that we’re supposed to follow no matter what. and i think that’s important! but i think in our late teens and early adulthood, we have to take it upon ourselves to find nuance in these rules. i’ve actually struggled in my life a little bit because i’ve felt this internal pressure to follow these fundamental rules i learned as a kid, and there was never a check-in moment where an adult told me that things aren’t always so black and white. i’ve sort of had to figure this out on my own. so today i’m gonna discuss a few of my discoveries about these rules, and i think there are some things that could even be beneficial to unlearn as an adult. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nepotism</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4bB6oMqFgml9PpJHZPyZo3</link>
      <guid>4bB6oMqFgml9PpJHZPyZo3</guid>
      <description>today we’re going talk about nepotism. now, what is nepotism? in simple terms, nepotism is getting a job or an opportunity because you know somebody in a relevant position of power. right now, the internet has been discussing nepotism in the entertainment industry. “nepotism babies” is the term coined for people who are famous because their family has connections to the entertainment industry. i think the internet as a whole is alarmed and frightened by how much of the entertainment industry is just nepotism. but i think it’s interesting because it can exist in any industry. if your parents went to a super prestigious college, there’s a good chance you can get in because they're alumni. so this exists everywhere, but why is it such a big deal in the entertainment industry? i need to put in my two cents. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mortality</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7D2R0FxdJH7H3jbSKEGtw4</link>
      <guid>7D2R0FxdJH7H3jbSKEGtw4</guid>
      <description>today's episode might get a little dark, okay? but we're going to get through it together. today we're talking about mortality. because me, you, everyone you know...we're all going to die at some point. i feel like when i was little, i knew i would die someday, but my perspective was kind of one dimensional and kind of optimistic. i felt like i had so much time. like, the narrative when i was a child was, 'ugh, you have so much time!' i just never really thought about my own mortality. but i think that part of maturing into adulthood is coming to terms with the fact that we're going to die and the people we love are going to die and it's fucking real. i just fully went through this realization recently and it has rocked my world. so today, we're going to talk about coming to terms with our mortality and how to process it in a healthy way. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2023 predictions </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4b7gSXVPuIbBfGG2jSqjPA</link>
      <guid>4b7gSXVPuIbBfGG2jSqjPA</guid>
      <description>happy 2023! here we go again. so today i want to talk about my 2023 predictions...what i think is going to happen this year. to be honest, i have no idea what i'm talking about, i have no evidence to back these predictions. so if you hear something and you're like, 'i don't think so' - you might be right. they're just predictions i've come up with, based on my own experiences and observations in life. some of them are predictions and some are more manifestations- like things that i want to happen...but i also can see them happening, you know? let's just get right into it!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>my philosophy on copying </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5kRzjhheK7Dy81AgwzPFba</link>
      <guid>5kRzjhheK7Dy81AgwzPFba</guid>
      <description>today we're going to talk about copying. the interesting thing about copying is...when people think about copying, most people think of it as a bad thing, but, in some instances, it can actually be an incredible thing. copying is definitely a complicated topic. so i wanted to talk about it today and discuss my philosophy on copying: when it's good, when it's bad, when it's useful, when it's evil, etc. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>is ignorance bliss? </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0LkKGSwqhYVX2cPbpxEcvW</link>
      <guid>0LkKGSwqhYVX2cPbpxEcvW</guid>
      <description>i would consider myself to be an observer of people-i'm constantly analyzing people and trying to understand what makes them tick. it helps me understand myself and the world better. something i've noticed about people is that they tend to fall into one of three categories: 1) people who are just aloof to the world around them and kind of clueless 2) people who are extremely aware of the world around them and very knowledgeable and 3) people who are somewhere in the middle. i've always wondered which extreme is a happier life: having a ton of knowledge and being super aware of the world around you? or being sort of ignorant to the world around you and just being free from complex issues? what's a happier life? that's what we're going to discuss today.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>post it or it didn't happen? </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5jifTitqdsFGweXDMfWwbB</link>
      <guid>5jifTitqdsFGweXDMfWwbB</guid>
      <description>recently i went to the harry styles concert in los angeles and it was amazing. the concert was incredible...but something did happen at this concert that was interesting. i was sitting kind of far up, so i could see the whole arena and when harry first came on, everybody took their phone out and started filming him...but then the phones never went down. this wave of phones just up in the air never stopped...and i started getting a weird feeling in my tummy...like, 'wait, maybe this is weird/a bad sign?' so i tried not to think about it, but then two weeks ago, i went to an event and, the same thing happened...everyone was taking photos and videos of everything. and i was like, 'this is actually weird.' it's become so routine and so normal, but i don't think that it actually is. so that's what i want to talk about today: why we are so obsessed with taking photos of everything? and why i think maybe we should stop.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>does money buy happiness? </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2slkV2HWx5BpzIrPIOZBjw</link>
      <guid>2slkV2HWx5BpzIrPIOZBjw</guid>
      <description>today we're going to talk about the age-old question: does money buy happiness. now i know you might be thinking, 'okay, emma, you're talking about something that you've kind of experienced.' i mean, i'm no billionaire, but i have made money in a way that i didn't know was possible. however, i don't really relate to a lot of people with money, since i still live a pretty normal life: i do my own dishes, i go grocery shopping, i wipe my cats butts, you know, normal things...all that's to say, i think i have perspective. i also did not grow up rich. i was fine, i always had everything i needed, but i was always comparing myself to my friends who were rich... it made me feel bad about myself because i didn't grow up with a lot of money. i used to think that if i got rich, i would be magically happier. so now that i've been on both sides, i want to talk about it...does money actually buy happiness? let's see.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dealing with difficult people </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6k5eavPWk26OirCMYAah3z</link>
      <guid>6k5eavPWk26OirCMYAah3z</guid>
      <description>we deal with difficult people every day...sometimes it's our family members, sometimes it's our friends, sometimes it's people at work or on the internet...no matter where you experience difficult people the most, you're definitely experiencing them. today i want to talk about how i deal with difficult people, how i prevent them from ruining my day and how i've gotten to a place where i feel kind of invincible when it comes to dealing with people, in general...i've gotten to a place where what other people do or say doesn't affect me very deeply anymore. i want to talk about it, because i think it's a really incredible skill to have and it saves you from a lot of pain and grief in life.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>sex </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0ErfTDz78ItR5MQp0Jt5LQ</link>
      <guid>0ErfTDz78ItR5MQp0Jt5LQ</guid>
      <description>today i wanted to talk about something rated r...something for adults only. so if you're not an adult, turn this podcast off and go catch up with cocomelon or caillou. for the adults, we're talking about sex. the big s-e-x. yeah, i know. i want to talk about all the ways that i was lied to about sex. growing up my first impression of what sex was came from movies, music videos and books. obviously your parents give you &quot;the talk,&quot; or school provides general sex ed, but that only tells you about the technical stuff. your first impression of what sex is really like was through different forms of entertainment. entertainment is always a little bit fantastical, it skips the boring stuff. the issue is that when young people are exposed to this stuff, their first impression of sex is that it's always spicy and perfect...and that just isn't true. at 21, i still find myself struggling with unlearning all the ideas i had about sex that were formed when i was younger, from the media i was consuming. so i want to dig into it today: all of the things that i had to unlearn about sex and the realities of sex that i've learned as an adult. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>does living in la help your career? </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5a4AmpBkzL0t7dGLEAEeKQ</link>
      <guid>5a4AmpBkzL0t7dGLEAEeKQ</guid>
      <description>i've been living in la for almost 5 years now. i grew up in northern california, and when i was 17 i moved to los angeles to pursue my career in the internet. i feel like now that i've been here for 5 years, i can really, finally discuss whether or not living in la actually helps your career. i really moved here just for my career- no other reason and i'm not the only one...a lot of people pursuing a career in entertainment move to la...it has the reputation of being the place where people in the entertainment industry can grow their career. i've gone back and forth about whether living here helps or hurts your career long term. so today, we're going discuss that and answer the big question: does living in la actually help your career?  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>seasonal depression </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2WKsgocbmXmVgwy2JOTBLV</link>
      <guid>2WKsgocbmXmVgwy2JOTBLV</guid>
      <description>it's starting to feel like fall and a little bit like winter where i live. over the last few weeks, i've really felt the shift: summer's over, it's gone. it's starting to get cold and dark and i'm feeling it, as i do every year. the fall/winter season challenges me mentally every year. every year, i'm convinced i'll be strong and not be affected by the changing of the season, but every year i get hit by a little bit of seasonal depression. this year it's hitting me medium hard. it's affecting me in a lot of different ways from being extra tired, to having less motivation...i kind of feel like shit, honestly. since it happens to me every year, i have finally come to expect and prepare for it. so i have some tips, based on how i handle my seasonal depression, for how to get through it and maybe they can be helpful to you, too. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i changed my mind</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/22BuGNcsLhd5Z9FuSutSOS</link>
      <guid>22BuGNcsLhd5Z9FuSutSOS</guid>
      <description>if you are a frequent listener of anything goes, you know i love talking about life, life philosophy, society as whole, etc... i like sharing my opinions, discussing those things broadly and openly. there's two things about that: 1) i don't know everything and 2) i'm 21 and i'm still learning a lot and so naturally, i'm not always going to get it right. sometimes i will get it right, but i'm not always going to get it right and i am open to that. so in today's episode, i'm going to address some of the times when people disagreed with me heavily and i'm going to talk about it. i'm going to talk about whether i still stand by what i said, or if maybe my opinion has changed. i wanted to do this, because i feel like a lot of people are afraid of the natural and healthy evolution of the human mind over the course of your life where your ideas and your moral compass change over time. it can be humbling because you have to admit that you were wrong or didn't know enough about a topic at the time, but it's so so important. let's get into it.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>would you rather: fashion edition </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4KgLhN9j6T7kb3JFRRYvTj</link>
      <guid>4KgLhN9j6T7kb3JFRRYvTj</guid>
      <description>i go through different phases with clothing. sometimes i'm in a phase where i'm obsessed with clothes and fashion but then some other times, i couldn't care less, and clothing and fashion are the last things on my mind. well, right now, at this present moment, i'm in this phase where all i can think about is clothes. i spend so much of my free time making mood boards, putting together outfits just for fun...for whatever reason, i'm just in this phase. and i thought, in honor of my current fashion excitement, we could play a game of 'would you rather: fashion edition.' feel free to play along at home, i think we're going to have a lot of fun today.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cheating </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4hww4ceGsxIOqvTfo9iLVd</link>
      <guid>4hww4ceGsxIOqvTfo9iLVd</guid>
      <description>we're talking about something serious today...anyone who has been on the internet recently has been seeing this conversation about people who cheat on their significant others in a relationship. it seems a lot of people have gotten caught cheating recently and because of that, it feels like cheating has been a big topic of discussion on the internet. so i wanted to talk about cheating today because it's a complicated subject. when i was younger, i used to think it was just always wrong and anyone who did it was terrible, but as i get older, i'm starting to realize that topics like cheating are much more complex than i originally thought when i was a child. so that's what i want to talk about the nuances of cheating- why people do it, whether it can ever be forgiven and whether once a cheater, always a cheater is actually true. here we go. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>celebrity privacy </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5xJg5K3B8FnNcM2GZaYvLH</link>
      <guid>5xJg5K3B8FnNcM2GZaYvLH</guid>
      <description>i feel like every day at least once, i catch myself reading an article about celebrity drama. and every once in a while, i'll look in the comments section...and i've noticed a theme: there are two types of comments. some comments are just about the situation being reported on, you know, people putting in their two cents, sharing their opinion, etc. the other comments are people saying, ‘take this down and stop talking about this person's private life.’ no matter what the situation is, there are these two types of comments. and this just really got me thinking about this argument...how much privacy do celebrities deserve? and it is a complicated, complicated dilemma. so i wanted to deep dive into the dilemma today, share my thoughts, opinions, have an open conversation and see what conclusion we come to, if any. we probably won't come to a conclusion, but it's just something really interesting to dissect.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>choosing between love and career… can you have both?</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/034I64yeiDCiSeF0okHFJg</link>
      <guid>034I64yeiDCiSeF0okHFJg</guid>
      <description>i've noticed that a lot of gen z and millennial people seem to be choosing their career over love. there seems to be this sort of belief within young people that you can't have both and need to choose one or the other. i've kind of seen this narrative float around a bit on the internet and in person and it really got me thinking: is this true? do you have to choose one? do you have to choose being in love and being in a relationship or building a successful career? or can you have both? upon reflecting upon my own life, and thinking for a while, i realized i disagree with this idea. i think that relationships don't have to prevent success at all, in fact, i think being in a good relationship can nurture success. so that's what we're talking about today. we’re going to go over why i think this is true and why it could be true for you, too.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> is anyone actually cool?</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/12U9dxlcqZ6ZMbplUo8bld</link>
      <guid>12U9dxlcqZ6ZMbplUo8bld</guid>
      <description>something i (and probably you) have struggled with our whole lives is thinking other people are cooler than us. seeing someone on social media or at a party and thinking, 'god, why are they so much cooler than me?' it's just a part of life. but recently, i have come to the conclusion that i don't think anyone is that cool. i think some people are just better than others at creating an illusion that they're cool. i actually might argue that the concept of coolness that we've all been living by our whole lives is a lie. the idea of coolness we have is completely fake. i would argue this. and that's what we're going to talk about today. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>temptation </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1kYRqNbKSIvq8zs6bH6WRz</link>
      <guid>1kYRqNbKSIvq8zs6bH6WRz</guid>
      <description>today we're going to be talking about temptation. which, in my opinion, is one of the most challenging things we deal with as human beings. it's something we deal with whether we're 2 years old or 102 years old. the temptations can change as we get older, but some form of it is always there. the reason i think it's so hard to deal with, is because in the short term, it's often easier and more fun- there's instant gratification. the problem is, usually things that are tempting, that you know are wrong, will end up leaving you miserable down the line. no one gets away with it - the universe doesn't work like that. i feel like it's the fighting of a temptation that helps you grow into a more morally solid person. it's so important for your self-development, self-esteem and more...recently i had my own sort of awakening with resisting temptation that really clicked for me and that's what i want to talk about today. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>traveling for a month… </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/70qpdrThZKagbmOvXsWyiR</link>
      <guid>70qpdrThZKagbmOvXsWyiR</guid>
      <description>so for the last month of my life i have been traveling...i've been living out of a literal carry-on suitcase for an entire month. it's the longest i've ever traveled and while, overall, it's an incredible experience, it also isn't a perfect experience, because nothing in life really ever is. i kind of wanted to shed some light on what it's really like to travel for a long period of time. i want to share what i've learned - the best things about it, the things that can be hard and some little tips and tricks to make your long-term travel more enjoyable and sustainable. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pet peeves #3</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2cZTws8wYT6yW7c3TM0nwu</link>
      <guid>2cZTws8wYT6yW7c3TM0nwu</guid>
      <description>today we're talking about pet peeves. i have done this a couple times on the show, where i talk about my pet peeves and just list them off. but it has been a while and i have a whole new list. i have so many more pet peeves...things that just piss me off, things that make me angry, things that have been bothering me and i am going to share them all today. why? there's literally no reason. there's no deeper meaning, no philosophical value, i just want to vent about what's been annoying me. maybe you guys will agree? maybe you will feel understood and related to. but that's what we're doing today. here we go. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>balance in relationships </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/32MelKonsLy7OkLcrO5gOb</link>
      <guid>32MelKonsLy7OkLcrO5gOb</guid>
      <description>well, my cats woke me up at 3am and i couldn't fall back asleep, so i am coming to you at 5:30am and the thing on my mind is relationships...i haven't talked about relationships in a long time and i wanted to bring them up again because they are fascinating to me. it's just so interesting when two people get together...like, why did those two people choose each other? i analyze this constantly. so today i want to talk about two relationship dilemmas that i think are not talked about enough: 1) finding balance when it comes to dealing with your own issues in a relationship, and 2) having independence in a relationship. i am going to share what i've learned about these two dilemmas and we will have a conversation about it. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>trendy or timeless #2</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7KOtLFzV9gUa5sqeKnphxi</link>
      <guid>7KOtLFzV9gUa5sqeKnphxi</guid>
      <description>today we're doing something fun. today we're going to take a look at some of the fashion trends that are happening right now, and we're going to discuss them. then i am going to decide whether i think the trend is trendy and it will dissipate at some point...or whether it's timeless and it's something that will stick around for years to come. that's today's episode. i actually did this type of episode before, honestly maybe a year ago, but i think there's new trends happening now, so it's time to do it again. let's get started! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>failure (part 2: failing in our endeavors)</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1p0OuDdEB3X7B7yUNgo1Kz</link>
      <guid>1p0OuDdEB3X7B7yUNgo1Kz</guid>
      <description>welcome back for part two of my series on failure. the first episode in this series was about failing as a human being. this episode is a little bit different because it's actually about failing in your endeavors. maybe that's job-related, something creative, school-related, a new hobby...failing in our endeavors in life. right now in our society, it's hard to fail...it kind of feels like there's no room for it. so i want to share some tools i've found that makes trying something new easier or a little more enjoyable and decreases the fear of failure. here we go. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>failure (part 1: failing as a human being)</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6Q5YP1pqVvoJ01m8WdfMHN</link>
      <guid>6Q5YP1pqVvoJ01m8WdfMHN</guid>
      <description>hi. for the next two episodes i'm going to be doing a little two part series about failure. i wanted to do this because i think it's really easy to forget that failing in anything in life doesn't define you. it doesn't make you a permanently evil person, it doesn't make you a permanent loser or a permanent idiot. failing actually has a crucial role in becoming a better you in all areas of life. i think a lot of us know that, but it's easy to forget. so today i want to remind you, and talk about failing as a human being...about personal failure to yourself and others. we'll go over types of personal failure, the lessons we learn from failure, how to handle it and move on from it, failure in relationships and more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>stuff i've been loving #2 (i still have a shopping problem)</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0pgmKJMWrBFdqyOwpEIQlk</link>
      <guid>0pgmKJMWrBFdqyOwpEIQlk</guid>
      <description>another episode with more things that you didn't ask for but you absolutely need in your life. some of these you may hate me for but i swear they will make your life so much better. clothing items, beauty products, apps, and pistachios that have changed my life. seriously. they're amazing. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>plastic surgery</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6GL2hTW6FDdBa5ypfNrCEe</link>
      <guid>6GL2hTW6FDdBa5ypfNrCEe</guid>
      <description>hello. so i got to go to fancy event recently…and that’s great, but unfortunately that day, i was just not feeling myself…i was feeling a little insecure and not too cute. and the thing about fancy events is people always take a lot of photos and that happened there…there were some pictures taken of me at the event that i was not a fan of that kept getting reposted and honestly, i had a little freak out. i was really struggling with my self-image. and that got me thinking about plastic surgery and cosmetic procedures…what are the negatives, positives and should you tell someone about them? so i am talking all about that, including how i feel about them and whether i would ever get one. honestly, it’s kind of a layered topic, but i love talking this stuff out with you.   Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>criticism </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0sKNd2qI528UbMLfySdCmF</link>
      <guid>0sKNd2qI528UbMLfySdCmF</guid>
      <description>hello- today we’re talking about criticism. i think criticism is so important in all of its forms. i experience criticism a lot, and have actually learned to appreciate it. it’s possible to benefit rather than suffer from criticism. i share what i see as the distinction between helpful criticism and hurtful criticism, how i think criticism is best given, how i think criticism is best received, and more of my thoughts on the topic. how do you handle criticism? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>parties</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/10lBPh735WncSBiXcaJPZX</link>
      <guid>10lBPh735WncSBiXcaJPZX</guid>
      <description>hi guys. so a few months ago i read the great gatsby, which is a really good book- highly recommend. well, without spoiling the storyline for you, i will tell you that in this book, there are some extravagant parties. i mean, just gorgeous parties. at the end of reading the book i found myself craving a party. in the book parties seem perfect…but i’ve found that in reality, parties are less than perfect. in fact, they can sometimes be straight up not fun. so today, i want to talk about parties. i want to talk about my experiences, what could make parties better, and ways to make them more fun. let me know what you think and if you agree. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>health and wellness products, are they worth it?</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4fTF4rCoAJ8sSavUd9DTWv</link>
      <guid>4fTF4rCoAJ8sSavUd9DTWv</guid>
      <description>okay guys, here’s something you may not know about me: i have a tendency to be a bit of a sucker for health and wellness products that are kind of hyped up…and there’s a reason you may not know this about me…it’s because i kind of hate to admit it. i’m a little embarrassed that i feel the need to try every new vitamin, hair mask, face roller, moisturizer, what-have-you. so since i'm kind of an unintentional health and wellness product connoisseur, and out of guilt for purchasing all of these hyped up products, i wanted to share my thoughts about them. today i will go down the list of some of the most popular health and wellness rituals and products and share my true and honest thoughts on them. hopefully this will help so you don’t waste your time and money doing things that aren’t worth your time and money. maybe it will give you some ideas about the products that are worth it, too. let’s get into it. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>female friendships </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5tiXtum2xH5HIdfXvsrZwm</link>
      <guid>5tiXtum2xH5HIdfXvsrZwm</guid>
      <description>i really can only think about two things right now: number one, how good spicy dill pickle almonds are and number two, today’s topic, which is female friendships. i have done episodes about friendship, in general, on the show but recently i’ve been really thinking specifically about friendships between women. i think there’s a very special dynamic between two women who are friends- between anyone, really- but especially between women. so today i am going to share my personal experiences…why sometimes these friendships were harder for me as a kid and how they have gotten better as i’ve gotten older. i share my opinion on some of the tough parts of female friendships and also ways to overcome them so that you have a better relationship with your friends and yourself.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>making a comfortable space</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3cLcGDzrIUuhMdoL4T3lkb</link>
      <guid>3cLcGDzrIUuhMdoL4T3lkb</guid>
      <description>hi. i’ve been moving over the course of the past few months and i finally feel like i’m settled in a place i’ll be in for a while. in the past, i never really cared about the space i lived it- i just figured i’d be in and out in a year and there was no point. but with my new home, i really made an effort to make my space work for me and it has made me so much happier. so i have some tips i’m going to share, that you can use to make your space your own, too. it’s all about knowing yourself - it’s these little elements of personalization that make your day-to-day life easier and more streamlined…it’s kind of fun in a way. it’s enjoyable. hope these tips help…let me know if any of this stuff works for you. maybe i’m losing my marbles a bit, but i don’t know, i think it makes a big difference. love ya. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>what i’ve been wearing recently</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1aSIaK5EB9u5wA4RcLfMBb</link>
      <guid>1aSIaK5EB9u5wA4RcLfMBb</guid>
      <description>hi guys- i feel like i’m going through a sort of clothing renaissance right now, on a personal level…i also feel like i don’t really know what the word renaissance means, but it seems right, maybe? anyway, today we’re going to be talking about clothes- i’m sharing what i love wearing right now…what styles and types of clothes excite me, that kind of thing. i have lots of suggestions on places to buy these types of clothes and accessories, how i like putting together outfits these days and even some predictions on what the shoe of the summer will be. i had a lot of fun doing this episode. i love shooting the shit about clothes. can’t wait to hear your take on my recent faves and any clothing items you’re currently obsessed with.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>weed</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1FP8ms5fwfE20T4cW0umB4</link>
      <guid>1FP8ms5fwfE20T4cW0umB4</guid>
      <description>well, my cats woke me up at 5 in the morning, so i am coming to you early in the am to tell you my weed story. in the last episode, we talked about alcohol. i briefly mentioned that i do not smoke weed. today i’m going to tell you why and share my stories about my experiences with weed…why I don’t smoke weed, why i will never do it again and how it affects my anxiety. actually, i will not make any promises, because i don’t really trust myself, i might try it again, but it’s very unlikely and i really shouldn’t…anyway, now that i’m 21 i’m finally getting to tell you guys all the stories i always wanted to share. it’s honestly been so fun. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>alcohol </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/445MokPS5nyXM5iUY6WX7D</link>
      <guid>445MokPS5nyXM5iUY6WX7D</guid>
      <description>guess who just turned 21 years old? me. and you know what that means. i can legally drink in the usa. it’s nice…i mean, it has some pros, for sure, but it also has some cons. it’s also a little overwhelming to figure out your relationship with alcohol, especially in social situations and with your mental health. so i wanted to share some things with you that i wish i’d known before i started drinking…my thoughts on the positives and negatives of alcohol and even a few drinking tips. if you guys are also new to drinking, or even if you’ve been drinking for a while, maybe this will help.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>there is a culture shift coming (part 3: trends)</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3OmvCacnDk4O6xTcFBw1x2</link>
      <guid>3OmvCacnDk4O6xTcFBw1x2</guid>
      <description>hey guys, i have two things to tell you: i have a swollen eyeball, and also, this is the last episode of our three part series on culture. today we’re talking about trends and trend cycles- and how they’re changing. once again, i don’t know, you guys, i don’t know if anything i am saying today makes sense, but hopefully one thing did. anyway, i think that the trend cycle is no longer working in the way that it once did and i think that it actually might be a good thing. we’ll see. love you. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>there is a culture shift coming (part 2: mainstream celebrities)</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2pap8qHATMn4elx0tBLTBW</link>
      <guid>2pap8qHATMn4elx0tBLTBW</guid>
      <description>well guys, i’m back and i’m thinking about culture again and how it’s changing. this week is part two of my three part series and today i want to talk with you about mainstream celebrities…what a mainstream celebrity even is, how we viewed mainstream celebrities in the past and how i think we will view them in the future. i actually think there might be something really cool in store…or maybe i’m way off. i don’t know, but it is interesting and i’m excited to see what happens next.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>there is a culture shift coming (part 1: social media)</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6GEQvhmL87Rbe6lP6EJwOP</link>
      <guid>6GEQvhmL87Rbe6lP6EJwOP</guid>
      <description>culture affects all of us, every day. probably more than we think. but i think a big cultural shift is coming. so over the next three episodes, i want talk it through with you guys on how it may be changing. today’s episode is about social media…the way we use it, the meaning of “celebrity”, why i think it will all change again soon, and what this means for all of us. i’m fine with whatever happens, i’m honestly just here for the ride. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the pressure to overachieve</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6bfJY7NKGaA6SLvmoOmkPI</link>
      <guid>6bfJY7NKGaA6SLvmoOmkPI</guid>
      <description>ever get that feeling like no matter how much you do, it isn’t enough? ever since high school i’ve been beating myself up over that. i think a lot of us feel this pressure to overachieve and it really weighs on us. so i want to talk it through with you guys. i’ll share my tips on how i got past it, how to know yourself better, do you best (whatever that is) and to find a little joy in your life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>coachella 2022</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0bo4ojyQma2pfEUVszLS8a</link>
      <guid>0bo4ojyQma2pfEUVszLS8a</guid>
      <description>i’ve been sweating and breathing dust for three straight days and my feet are covered in blisters which can only mean i just got back from coachella. there is obviously so much hype around coachella so i’m going to give you guys the pros and cons, recap what happened this year, and give you some tips and tricks so you can thrive at your next music festival Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>a series of unfortunate events</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0W1Ciz5PkLdBeVriAMFQXE</link>
      <guid>0W1Ciz5PkLdBeVriAMFQXE</guid>
      <description>y’all i’ve been going through it the past two months. you know when everything that can go wrong, does? that’s literally been my life. some of the things that have been happening to me are just so ridiculous i had to share them with you guys. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>body image &amp; self-acceptance</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/328gUKa2Mt1xSEZ5TDfJ1U</link>
      <guid>328gUKa2Mt1xSEZ5TDfJ1U</guid>
      <description>this one is a bit different. normally before i do episodes i have everything all figured out (ok at least i try to). gonna be real with you guys, i don’t have all the answers here. i’ve dealt with this issue for years, and it’s been quite a journey, but i’ve learned a lot that i want to share that can hopefully help some of you. let’s work on it together. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i'm yolo'ing right now...</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5nRLfpIWRwIbn39IGxtXVc</link>
      <guid>5nRLfpIWRwIbn39IGxtXVc</guid>
      <description>you know i hate that i’m using the phrase yolo but honestly it’s the best way to describe my attitude towards life lately. i’ve just been getting a little crazy and living life, so i’ll tell you all about it. it may or may not have contributed to me getting 10 tattoos. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>standing up for yourself</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6RW0LWOvvOONsKVsBf8cSU</link>
      <guid>6RW0LWOvvOONsKVsBf8cSU</guid>
      <description>for so long i struggled with being a pushover and a yes man. i hated conflict, i hated thinking people could be angry with me, and i let people walk all over me. it sucked, and i know a lot of people struggle with this too. finally i had enough and started standing up for myself, and all those fears i had about how people would react never actually happened. so i’m here to help you guys out with the confidence to do it too, and explain why it’s the best thing you can do for yourself. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>stuff i've been loving #1</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/67P88HtAl1QYwka0tW1AT5</link>
      <guid>67P88HtAl1QYwka0tW1AT5</guid>
      <description>hello. i feel like lately i've been doing topics that are challenging to talk about. the last few episodes have been heavy and thought-provoking, and that's great...but today, i want to be not-so-deep. i think it's important to do that sometimes. in your 20s, you're questioning and deeply analyzing everything, i know i am. but today, i don't want to do that. i want to talk about the things i've been loving lately: what products i've been loving, the activities i've been loving, the snacks i've been loving--just the stuff i'm enjoying right now. i think that this could be helpful because maybe you might hear something i talk about today and think, 'i want to try that.' or maybe you have a recommendation for me that you'll dm me after the podcast. either way, it's going to be fun. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>integrity</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3UhgsuUfREwlrdmYmHObag</link>
      <guid>3UhgsuUfREwlrdmYmHObag</guid>
      <description>a lot of people have cheated their way to the top in this world. people have fucked over others, or lied to get ahead, and for what? fame they didn’t know what to do with? power but with a terrible conscious? and we’ve all been tempted to do it, me included. but i think there’s something to be said for going about life doing things the right way. maybe you won’t get ahead as fast, but you will eventually, and you’ll be in a much better place when you do get there. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pet peeves #2</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5SuUcYjaopMl1ecbPreJxW</link>
      <guid>5SuUcYjaopMl1ecbPreJxW</guid>
      <description>i had a lot of pet peeves last time we did one of these, i have a lot more now, and tbh i still have more after this episode but we’ll save those for another time. we all have pet peeves, i probably have more than most, like all the annoying things people do, the foods that make me absolutely gag, and how annoying is captcha? sorry apple watch people you don’t get a pass here either. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the truth about youtube</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0aBOcPKuUirp5sIt9d0VAv</link>
      <guid>0aBOcPKuUirp5sIt9d0VAv</guid>
      <description>as most of you guys know youtube has been a major part of my life. it's literally why i am where i am today. but my relationship with it has been rocky, and it's definitely taken a toll on me. so i want to open up about all of it, and talk to you guys about where i see my relationship with youtube in the future, and the things i want to focus on now. and for those of you who have been there since the early days of my channel, i can't thank you enough :) Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>stepping out of your comfort zone</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1L9EmE6au8oSbNbcvLNdmc</link>
      <guid>1L9EmE6au8oSbNbcvLNdmc</guid>
      <description>life lately has allowed a lot of us to just stay in our comfort zone. we can just text people instead of meeting them, we can get everything delivered instead of going in public, etc. but i think it’s time we start changing that a little. i just had a really enlightening experience getting out of my comfort zone recently after a traumatizing experience and wanted to share it with you guys, and give you some tips on stepping out of yours, and all the positive impacts it can have our lives. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>would you rather #2</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4gFTdn9FAJQPejoJwHvt1C</link>
      <guid>4gFTdn9FAJQPejoJwHvt1C</guid>
      <description>we did an episode like this a while back and you guys liked it and so did i so i decided to bring it back. you asked me a ton of would you rather questions and i answered them. deep philosophical questions, absolutely absurd questions, and questions that i hate that i had to answer but did anyways. i’m very glad i don’t actually have to make these decisions in real life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>having children</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5MbrXEEuVptzZ32nXwDcBH</link>
      <guid>5MbrXEEuVptzZ32nXwDcBH</guid>
      <description>there’s been a lot of talk lately about how get z and millennials are having kids less and less and i find it super interesting. some people know they want kids, some know they don’t, but i think a lot are just unsure. i’ve gone back and forth on whether or not i want kids myself. there are a lot of pros and cons of having them, so i’m talking it all through with you guys. also please don’t mind my minor meltdown throughout the episode about the yard work going on outside :) Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>good habits</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/08qDkNapT0ABcoW775c580</link>
      <guid>08qDkNapT0ABcoW775c580</guid>
      <description>seasonal affective disorder has been kicking in pretty hard these past few weeks… it’s cold, the sun is out for like 2 hours a day… so if you’re feeling kinda bummed out believe me you’re not alone. but i’ve picked up a few habits recently that have really helped me feel better and i wanna share with you guys. i know i sound like a mom and maybe not all of these will work for everyone but hopefully you’ll find at least a few of these tips helpful, not only for the winter time but year round.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the truth about being self-employed</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1BY6gLoK6BCDwvTS8CvuM9</link>
      <guid>1BY6gLoK6BCDwvTS8CvuM9</guid>
      <description>HAPPY TO BE BACK! i've seen a lot of talk on the internet about how amazing it is to be self-employed and how we should all strive for it, and turning your dream into a job is the key measure of success. as someone who is self-employed, i can definitely say it's not all it's glorified to be, so i'm talking through all the pros and cons of being self-employed, and why sometimes having a regular 9-5 isn't a bad thing at all. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>new years resolutions</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/31pUf2I7WOB6ZcEONdrmka</link>
      <guid>31pUf2I7WOB6ZcEONdrmka</guid>
      <description>ok, last episode for the year before i take a little break. i literally NEVER do new years resolutions, but i decided i'm doing some this year. i think they can help us to achieve things we've been wanting to work on. they don't have to be big, and they don't have to be difficult, so i'm going to lay out mine, and give you guys some tips on yours so you can stick with them. love you all see you in 2022 :) Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>friendships</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7Du9OLXbUrYpiDXqL7gQMu</link>
      <guid>7Du9OLXbUrYpiDXqL7gQMu</guid>
      <description>romantic relationships can be complicated, but so can friendships. ive been taking some time lately to reflect on what truly makes a good friendship. so this ep i'm going to explain the 6 criteria i think should be a part of a good friendship, so hopefully you guys can apply those to yours and re-evaluate some that aren't fulfilling. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>fashion advice</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/35m3QH5GLyOjDmGixBtUvu</link>
      <guid>35m3QH5GLyOjDmGixBtUvu</guid>
      <description>haven't done an advice session in a little while and wanted to do one that was focused on fashion especially with the holidays coming up. i'll answer all your questions on everything fashion related to get you guys looking and feeling your best. the episode is sponsored by macy's and you guys can check out my personal holiday shopping guide right here :) Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>getting back on track</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3Vi8OR1NcUIAvkcCV3Lng7</link>
      <guid>3Vi8OR1NcUIAvkcCV3Lng7</guid>
      <description>a few episodes ago i talked to you guys about an existential crisis i've been going through and let me tell you it's been rough. so i decided to take a day and work on pulling myself back together and it made me feel SO MUCH better. so i'm going to share my journey with you all and hopefully help you with some tips on how to get through a rough patch or a hard time. we all go through it but there are definitely some ways to get out of it. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>overrated v. underrated</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6Pmu5GAUrOoBzt0lqRCRu3</link>
      <guid>6Pmu5GAUrOoBzt0lqRCRu3</guid>
      <description>i wanted to play a game with you guys and you delivered. this was fun. you sent in things to discuss, and i'm giving my opinion on if they're overrated, underrated, or justified. everything from clothing and fashion trends, to workout classes, to living the stereotypical teenage dream. and something about a piece of toast with butter at midnight just hits different. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>identity</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7C4P0xoC8X0f1uRi6MmNA8</link>
      <guid>7C4P0xoC8X0f1uRi6MmNA8</guid>
      <description>our identity encompasses who we are. our passions, our inspirations, our personality, how we express ourselves, how we treat others. it’s constantly evolving. but understanding it can be hard. it can be confusing. it was for me, and i know it probably is for a lot of you too, so i wanna share my journey with you guys. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>existential crisis</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0YPmSFT5skgwUpTaR5S65q</link>
      <guid>0YPmSFT5skgwUpTaR5S65q</guid>
      <description>alright, not gonna lie, this one gets a little deep. i’ve been going through some shit, and it’s been tough. ever feel like you’re not sure what your purpose is? or what we’re all doing here? or what the meaning of everything is? you’re not alone if you have. i had a bit of an existential crisis, but it’s really helped to put things into perspective for me. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>holiday shopping?</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0IbLyaghzsXSSsOlYzone1</link>
      <guid>0IbLyaghzsXSSsOlYzone1</guid>
      <description>alright some people love holiday shopping and are really good at it, and some people hate it and think they’re terrible at it. no matter which side you’re on, i got you covered. all the best gifts you can get someone that are sure to go over well even for those people who are impossible to shop for. and all the things you need to avoid giving people. like live animals. why do people do that? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>competition is the thief of creativity</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6uyyiiNPcQnraF9M7khXSh</link>
      <guid>6uyyiiNPcQnraF9M7khXSh</guid>
      <description>this podcast was nominated for another people’s choice award which is AMAZING and i cannot thank you guys enough. so it’s only fitting that i do an episode about how much i hate award shows lol. kidding, kinda, but i don’t think someone’s creativity should be judged based on someone else’s opinions. sports and competitions, sure, but judging someone’s art as “good” or “bad” doesn’t make sense so i talk about it in this ep. and i finally share my story about what happened at the streamys a few years back. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>halloween</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/69GLVpsvOfYJOS68aHsOcr</link>
      <guid>69GLVpsvOfYJOS68aHsOcr</guid>
      <description>it's safe to say halloween hasn't always been my favorite holiday. there can be so much pressure on costumes, who dressed up like what, am i overdressed am i underdressed etc. it's stressful. BUT it can also be kinda fun, so i'm walking you guys through all the ways to approach halloween this year. types of costumes, some of my favorites that i've done, and what you can do last minute if you're going out. but if you decide you're not feeling getting dressed up, i got you with some other fun activities, recipes you can cook, and some favorite movies. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>alone but not lonely</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4mBgKq89nNMSRjlnCcZKWA</link>
      <guid>4mBgKq89nNMSRjlnCcZKWA</guid>
      <description>ok sorry this ep is late but we lost the first one i recorded and i havent felt heartbreak like that since a high school breakup… anyways a lot of people have been saying how sad it is that i’ve been spending a lot of time alone, but it’s what i need right now and honestly it’s changed my perspective on things allowed me to experience things i wouldn’t have otherwise. being alone isn’t a bad thing. also i think i found a hobby thats going to stick after getting obsessed with a youtube series.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice session #14</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3QBmu2ESoC3JnowbzvbRAM</link>
      <guid>3QBmu2ESoC3JnowbzvbRAM</guid>
      <description>i can’t believe we’ve done 14 of these already. i asked you guys to ask me questions about anything and you delivered. advice on how to not be overwhelmed when you have so much to do, when to move in with someone and when to wait (hint: wait if you can), dealing with social anxiety which i have plenty of experience with, hookup culture, and why you should do all the corny shit in the movies to romanticize your life :) Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>quality over quantity</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0YThGNgL46qBGNhPw4tds2</link>
      <guid>0YThGNgL46qBGNhPw4tds2</guid>
      <description>ok bear with me because i'm running on no sleep and drinking coffee right before bed BUT i've had a revelation recently in life about the phrase quality over quantity. we know quality is better, but i think quantity can also negatively impact us too. friendships, clothes, etc. we think we want more but honestly, it can end up hurting us in the end. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>travel tips</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6pE8SJRjQqvFghyCUPTYJv</link>
      <guid>6pE8SJRjQqvFghyCUPTYJv</guid>
      <description>well…. i lasted 4 days back in la and decided i needed to go back to nyc, so i’ve been traveling A LOT. needless to say i’ve picked up a lot of travel tips over the years that has made my life easier and i wanted to share with you guys. some boring but very useful packing tricks, how to plan things in advance, tips on traveling alone, and seriously plz stop going to cheesecake factory i beg you. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the feminine mold</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3iETGnuD0mYIQ45eRH1TGu</link>
      <guid>3iETGnuD0mYIQ45eRH1TGu</guid>
      <description>As we grow up we’re told there are certain molds and stereotypes that we need to fit into: the “ideal” woman, the “ideal” guy, etc. But that image in our minds can leave us feeling that we’re not good enough unless we achieve it. Emma talks through her struggles with this growing up, and the issues it caused with her self-esteem and how she was treated by others. Once we learn to accept who we are, and forget who we think we should be, then we can truly be happy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the met gala</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/11PsgzxwJyC60kjjMGXD24</link>
      <guid>11PsgzxwJyC60kjjMGXD24</guid>
      <description>Emma is back from one of the craziest few weeks of her life, filled with a rollercoaster of emotions. She talks all about all the details of her time at the Met Gala, and the entire process leading up to it: from getting the call she was going, to preparing and designing the dress with Louis Vuitton (and inspirations behind it), what actually happens at the event itself and after, and all of the feelings she’s had throughout. It's been a wild ride she's excited to share with everyone. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>back to school</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7gQBy9zZmM1veLZsEGl1ZK</link>
      <guid>7gQBy9zZmM1veLZsEGl1ZK</guid>
      <description>It’s that time of the year again. Some of us look forward to it, some of us dread it. Whichever situation you’re in, Emma has you covered as she shares all her tips and things she wish she knew heading into a new school year. From fitting into a social circle and finding the right friends, to dealing with new teachers, to getting involved with activities, and do grades really matter that much? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>products that have changed my life (i have a shopping problem)</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6uDhRNzbWhWQvJZIkyDCdc</link>
      <guid>6uDhRNzbWhWQvJZIkyDCdc</guid>
      <description>Emma is chatting about all of her favorite this week! From household items she can’t live without, to fun life-hack gadgets, to all of her favorite brands in beauty, fashion, and more. Plus, she’s answering questions on it all, including if certain expensive items are worth the price, which brands to choose for certain products, and more!Get 1 free month of Tinder Gold at https://tinder.com/vip/agpodcast Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice session #13 (relationships)</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7Mx2ddRmznxUTTppraIixu</link>
      <guid>7Mx2ddRmznxUTTppraIixu</guid>
      <description>hey guys, today we’re going to be doing an advice session completely dedicated to relationships because relationships are just my favorite thing to talk about in my personal life and on the podcast. i’m going to be giving you relationship advice to the best of my ability considering the fact that i’m 20 and probably don’t know what i’m talking about. per usual with these, i’m just doing my best, take it or leave it. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>a happy &amp; healthy life</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4uTLnCklbPIA2RDozUfTbT</link>
      <guid>4uTLnCklbPIA2RDozUfTbT</guid>
      <description>Who doesn’t want to be happy? There are a lot of things in life that can get us down, or have a negative impact on our emotions, but it doesn’t have to be that way. Emma is going through all of the characteristics of how to create happiness in our lives, from building meaningful relationships, to limiting our time on social media, and gives some examples of things we can all do to bring a little more joy to our day. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>rock bottom</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5KjL1KuuDHC2WPSwtxNoVc</link>
      <guid>5KjL1KuuDHC2WPSwtxNoVc</guid>
      <description>You may have noticed, Emma took a break from YouTube. For a while she was feeling uninspired and lacking creativity, and in this episode gets very introspective as to why she was feeling that way, and how it was casting some really dark clouds over her. Discussions on ways to become inspired again, finding your self-worth, and why hitting rock bottom isn’t the end. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>trendy or timeless #1</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0YpzFaUOg62bLu5irHeK2X</link>
      <guid>0YpzFaUOg62bLu5irHeK2X</guid>
      <description>For a while, Emma was uninspired by fashion, especially during Covid, but now she's gotten back into it and is talking about it all. From thoughts on latest fashion trends, how to be creative with fashion, what trends and timeless pieces are her favorites, and everything in between. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>regaining perspective</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0AT36Vz92Kgwwwx3bbZOXW</link>
      <guid>0AT36Vz92Kgwwwx3bbZOXW</guid>
      <description>Anxiety comes in a lot of different ways. Sometimes it can feel like the weight of it can be unbearable. Emma has been going through a lot lately, and shares some experiences on how putting things into perspective can really help us. Plus, tips and tricks on how to reduce our anxiety, how to deal with panic attacks when they come, and more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>things feel weird rn</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0Mu58GCtRs2AuxHmH6xIyP</link>
      <guid>0Mu58GCtRs2AuxHmH6xIyP</guid>
      <description>For some of us, the world is starting to open back up again. It’s something we’ve been looking forward to for so long, but that doesn’t mean the transition is easy. Emma is chatting this week about some of the struggles and anxieties associated with things getting back to normal. From not wearing masks indoors, feeling super drained in social situations, not having the energy to make plans, feeling awkward when reconnecting with people we haven’t seen in so long, and difficulties making new friends. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>success kills creativity</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3sSSlArj5c6c49p5WUMCoD</link>
      <guid>3sSSlArj5c6c49p5WUMCoD</guid>
      <description>We’ve seen it before… we find a band and their first album is amazing, they blow up, then their second album just doesn’t cut it. Or a TV show… we’re glued to the first season, then can’t even get through the second. Why does success kill creativity? Emma has experienced it herself, and this week she’s diving into why sometimes when we find success, it can be detrimental to continuing to be creative. She’ll talk about ways we can avoid it, and find the balance between creativity and success. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice session #12</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0wDWlc9aDkieMb5x2OOT0x</link>
      <guid>0wDWlc9aDkieMb5x2OOT0x</guid>
      <description>Emma is back giving advice on every topic you guys ask about. Things like setting goals to help achieve happiness, dealing with Imposter Syndrome, letting go of difficult relationships and keeping current ones exciting, feeling comfortable being our true selves, and more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>my spiritual journey </title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4LFXgfGVClGBuwj4Naqj6i</link>
      <guid>4LFXgfGVClGBuwj4Naqj6i</guid>
      <description>This week Emma is talking through her journey of religion and spirituality. While often it’s something that isn’t addressed, it can have a major impact on how we shape our lives. She chats through growing up being exposed to different religions, her beliefs and what has shaped them, how religion and spirituality impacts all of us, where her journey has taken her today, and everything in between. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>two weeks with no tiktok</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1q1zu2lOZS3sWbbKk4IAmX</link>
      <guid>1q1zu2lOZS3sWbbKk4IAmX</guid>
      <description>After using it every day for over a year, Emma finally deleted TikTok off her phone. While it may not seem like a big deal, it’s made a massive impact on her life. This episode she’s talking about all the ways eliminating distractions in our life can make it so much better. How removing things like a social media app that we waste our time on, or relationships that drain our energy, can give us the physical and mental space to do the things we really enjoy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>growing up as an only child</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0sJnxKq6KqGlDdRH0Tsb6P</link>
      <guid>0sJnxKq6KqGlDdRH0Tsb6P</guid>
      <description>Growing up as an only child is a really unique experience that can really have both positive and negative impacts on your life and relationships. From feelings of independence, desires to be alone more often than most, relating more to adults more than people your own age, difficulties sharing with others, and much more. Emma discusses her experience growing up as an only child and the differences vs. having siblings, and how that’s impacted her personality and her approach to life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>how am i really doing?</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2JoU5pJtuGFTd4Lfb5gsir</link>
      <guid>2JoU5pJtuGFTd4Lfb5gsir</guid>
      <description>Gossip and rumors have been floating around the internet about Emma’s mental health recently. While it’s lead to some positive reactions, it’s also lead to a lot of negativity and judgement. Emma is diving into the state of social media today, and how it plays into our mental health. Why do people find the need to stretch narratives and make up lies about others just for likes and retweets? And why are we so drawn to all the drama? Maybe it’s time to get off some of the apps… Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice session #11</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6yjRqKAQjfnHfEB38ce0CJ</link>
      <guid>6yjRqKAQjfnHfEB38ce0CJ</guid>
      <description>Answering more of your advice questions! Topics like figuring out if you should try to fix or just leave a toxic friendship, how to gain confidence with your personality and “attractiveness” regardless of what others may think ,if now is the time to focus on your career or relationships, ways to accept constructive criticism to improve parts of our lives, and many more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mind your own business</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/47Xt9or4VSeR4BYbil8VT5</link>
      <guid>47Xt9or4VSeR4BYbil8VT5</guid>
      <description>Often it can feel like drama is all around us, like it follows us and we can’t get away from it. Or, we find ourselves seeking it when we know it’s bad for us. This week Emma is chatting about all things drama: how it occurs, why we’re drawn to it, and provides insight an examples of how we can avoid it and live a much happier and stress-free life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>would you rather...</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2qKBjqGMJ2c1KAz4UjmMFN</link>
      <guid>2qKBjqGMJ2c1KAz4UjmMFN</guid>
      <description>This week Emma is pondering life’s most difficult questions in a game of Would You Rather? Debating topics like being cheated on or being the one cheating, having people show up at your wedding or funeral, joining a sorority or a content house, and many more. Plus, Emma drank WHAT during a dare?? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>growing HURTS</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4d0F7t7KVAbkHnPkZM6FsT</link>
      <guid>4d0F7t7KVAbkHnPkZM6FsT</guid>
      <description>Most of us have some things we want to work on in our lives, and Emma is chatting through all of that this episode. From thing she’s been working on, ways to improve our self-esteem, when is it time to be alone and self-reflect vs. being around people, positive things we can do to be better people and improve our lives, and some tips on being happier and feeling more fulfilled.   Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>break up? or no break up?</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/070xKp6PONJEdzb0nWN5MB</link>
      <guid>070xKp6PONJEdzb0nWN5MB</guid>
      <description>Emma is analyzing all types of fan relationship situations, and giving her thoughts on how to approach it. Friendships, romantic relationships, even relationships with peers. Weighing the pros and cons of significant others, handling long distance, what to do if friends feel manipulative, even how to approach a situation where someone gets pregnant. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice session #10</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2VeP1zl2XIboi26lJNz29Y</link>
      <guid>2VeP1zl2XIboi26lJNz29Y</guid>
      <description>Emma is back giving advice on more of your questions! Advice on following passions how to know what career path to take, making new friends and also recognizing when to move away from friendships that aren’t working, when to know that it’s time to get into a relationship, and how do we act during those awkward moments when someone is crying. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>we need to read books</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7HuWkFnLZ4VIM689k6L5bJ</link>
      <guid>7HuWkFnLZ4VIM689k6L5bJ</guid>
      <description>Emma had a few life realizations this week that can hopefully help everyone else out. Why reading is really good for you, learning to find the positives where you live, and when is gossiping OK? Plus, questions on staying focused, how to feel independent, and what we should look for in a life partner. And the new SZA and Doja Cat is crazy fun.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the instagram illusion</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1ZTAE8edwNJafDgjtkN2qj</link>
      <guid>1ZTAE8edwNJafDgjtkN2qj</guid>
      <description>This week Emma is talking all things Instagram. Social media can have a lot of pros, but it can also have a lot of cons. From the benefits and why we’re so drawn to it, to the negative effect it can have on our self-esteem and our perceptions of others. How we can manage our use of Instagram, get the most of it, and when is it time to take a break? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>traveling alone</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6IfB9CMkrx28rYvFOYTo42</link>
      <guid>6IfB9CMkrx28rYvFOYTo42</guid>
      <description>Emma is back from a much needed solo trip to NYC. She chats through it and discusses the benefits of traveling alone, even if it’s outside of our comfort zone, when we need a little reset. Plus, why being alone can be beneficial, how to be comfortable being alone if you aren’t used to it, and some tips on doing some self-reflection. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>exposing myself</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/37MUJVrHhax1xq5H2Pix7M</link>
      <guid>37MUJVrHhax1xq5H2Pix7M</guid>
      <description>We've all had some pretty embarrassing moments in our lives. Emma has had plenty, and she's here to share them all. From awkward kiss experiences, to the things her cleaning lady finds under her bed, and what is she doing while in bed with someone else??? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice session #9</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6pjV85uur0GEJFjHUSd0dq</link>
      <guid>6pjV85uur0GEJFjHUSd0dq</guid>
      <description>Emma is back with another advice session, answering everyone’s questions! Topics like how to stop caring about your significant other’s ex, dealing with anxiety getting back into social situations, getting adventurous with your outfits, keeping strong relationships with divorced parents, how to navigate the friend zone, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>celebrity culture</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2kuRS2NLGuE9UpiSDQ6kAD</link>
      <guid>2kuRS2NLGuE9UpiSDQ6kAD</guid>
      <description>A lot of us grow up wanting to be famous, but is fame really all it’s cracked up to be? Having gotten a little taste of popularity in her own world, Emma talks about what it’s like having a following and being in the public spotlight. Plus, what it’s like for other major celebrities who are being scrutinized 24/7, with almost no privacy. What happens behind the scenes, the effect it has on your relationships and your mental health, and why so many people in the constant spotlight get addicted to substances. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>acne</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6OK9ZBtR1QyIE5nxg0wlBM</link>
      <guid>6OK9ZBtR1QyIE5nxg0wlBM</guid>
      <description>Acne is something a lot of us have dealt with or are dealing with currently. For some, it can be really difficult. Emma has had her own well-documented journey with acne, but it took a really serious toll on her both physically and mentally. She shares her entire story, from dealing with a ton of confidence issues, to depression, to all of the frustrations of treatments that weren’t working, and finally overcoming it. She shares tips on managing acne, how to get through it, and how to stay confident with it. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>fashion</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7N1tCGAoYw6a4Wj7P8KbmN</link>
      <guid>7N1tCGAoYw6a4Wj7P8KbmN</guid>
      <description>Over the years Emma has built her fashion identity and shared it all over the internet. This episode she talks about that journey and shares advice on how everyone can find their own fashion identity. From awkward stages, to inspiration, to trends, and carving your own way despite what others may think. Questions on staple pieces, where to spend your money (and where to save) and how to create your own look that unique to you. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>travel</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5kcl7v3elnvJktbcFe0X3K</link>
      <guid>5kcl7v3elnvJktbcFe0X3K</guid>
      <description>As most of us do, Emma misses traveling. So, she dives into it this week and gets excited to travel when it’s safe to do so. Everything from favorite vacations, worst places to visit, wild travel stories, best travel tips, and everything in between. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>healthy relationships</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7HFs1m604cJll1lzXwIcA3</link>
      <guid>7HFs1m604cJll1lzXwIcA3</guid>
      <description>Healthy relationships are hard to come by, can be difficult to maintain, and take a lot of effort. But, Emma has found all the keys to a healthy relationship based on her experiences. Tips on how to find them, ways to keep them strong, when to notice one isn’t working, and avoiding toxic relationships. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>unpopular opinions</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5fB9Sy93WwBFYVd9FrQPO4</link>
      <guid>5fB9Sy93WwBFYVd9FrQPO4</guid>
      <description>You have unpopular opinions, and Emma has responses to all of them. Everything from marriage and relationships, school and formal education, if TikTokers are actually talented, and is sex overrated? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice session #8</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5Gb9lvAMbRSxQ1SD1Spors</link>
      <guid>5Gb9lvAMbRSxQ1SD1Spors</guid>
      <description>It's another advice session! Answering questions on trust issues in friendships, how much time should you be spending with your significant other, and are you actually into that person or are they just hot?  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>life burnout</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5CroFt0EQ3sPdkYfqfxa2z</link>
      <guid>5CroFt0EQ3sPdkYfqfxa2z</guid>
      <description>It’s been a rough year, and all of us to some extent are feeling a sense of burnout in our lives. Whether that be a lack of motivation to do anything, or feeling down and sad, or having no desire to be social with anyone. Emma is going through it too, and discusses why it happens and ways we can overcome it.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>success</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2yRokDM7IYXz3VsDhm5Uts</link>
      <guid>2yRokDM7IYXz3VsDhm5Uts</guid>
      <description>Success comes in all forms, and means something different to everyone. Some may view it as popularity, or money, or something else. Emma chats through it all, from her successes as an influencer and how she views it, to how others perceive it, and how it can change us. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>basic isn't bad</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/13ZduA2jS5eEkJuQHXdAMs</link>
      <guid>13ZduA2jS5eEkJuQHXdAMs</guid>
      <description>Emma is back in the new year discussing her new found obsession with cooking, her recent experiences with therapy, and a few important life lessons she’s learned. Plus, why we shouldn’t rely on people in our lives, how do we define relationships, and are we getting a hair change soon? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>new years</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0jYzTaQx2RdVjDbK1QQtrD</link>
      <guid>0jYzTaQx2RdVjDbK1QQtrD</guid>
      <description>The end of 2020 is finally here, so Emma is talking all things New Years. From New Years Eve party stories, to reflecting on everything that she’s gone through this year, and looking ahead to some New Years Resolutions. Plus, she shares a story about getting away for a week and why being away from your phone is so important.   Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice session #7</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/72xdBJb1AS5LZsB2GEFE22</link>
      <guid>72xdBJb1AS5LZsB2GEFE22</guid>
      <description>The final advice session of 2020! Emma is giving her take on all of your questions, from thoughts on moving in with a significant other, to issues with being affectionate with people, to TikTok addictions and why it causes so much anxiety, and much more! Plus, Emma talks thorough getting ready for her therapy appointment.   Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>divorce</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0R1c7TuNjeCApUiIic69I9</link>
      <guid>0R1c7TuNjeCApUiIic69I9</guid>
      <description>Many of us have grown up with divorced parents, or lived through a divorce. Emma can relate, and she opens up about all of it. From the challenges of being stuck between two parents, living in different places, trying maintaining healthy relationships with both, awkward holidays, emotional struggles, and everything in between. Plus, Emma shares a first date experience and talks through ways to make them less awkward. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i can't talk to people anymore</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5kr2k2isXsURj2uKA2Oju0</link>
      <guid>5kr2k2isXsURj2uKA2Oju0</guid>
      <description>If you’ve been feeling extremely anti-social lately, you’re not alone. Emma is chatting about how quarantine has killed our desires to be social, and why she can only tolerate a handful of people right now. Plus, an embarrassing encounter with a celebrity while exercising, and Emma’s parents have been staying with her for over a month and it’s getting a bit…much. And questions on how to fix the school system, and if we should reconsider marriage? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>hobbies</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4NjVo4WHtym63Sr8VLDvOS</link>
      <guid>4NjVo4WHtym63Sr8VLDvOS</guid>
      <description>Sometimes, especially now, it can feel like we’re stuck in the same rut doing things that don’t bring us much joy. Thankfully Emma has picked up a few hobbies, and talks about the importance of doing something for the sole purpose of making us happy. Plus, a holiday gift-giving guide for everyone in your life, and questions on the problem with public relationships, Emma’s full list of celebrity crushes, and what’s going to happen in 2021? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>why i deleted twitter</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2TrCybv3yCKXZn7iZHOJGB</link>
      <guid>2TrCybv3yCKXZn7iZHOJGB</guid>
      <description>Emma opens up about the effects of negativity on the internet, spreading rumors and false information, and sheds light on why she recently deactivated her Twitter. Plus, questions on when do know if it’s time to be in a relationship, why we’re having such a hard time seeing into the future, and should you really be buying that guy or girl a Christmas gift?? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice session #6</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4OdD26hOeHrDbpQ306jwOz</link>
      <guid>4OdD26hOeHrDbpQ306jwOz</guid>
      <description>Another advice session! Emma is weighing in on a variety of things, like how to give great gifts without spending money during the holidays, tips on how boost confidence when feeling insecure, questions about sexuality and virginity, is it better to date around or try to stay with one person long term, and plenty more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the real reason i moved to LA</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/59oHZb3os4QWmMUKid0fjm</link>
      <guid>59oHZb3os4QWmMUKid0fjm</guid>
      <description>After 2 years, Emma can finally share the wild (and scary) story that finally led her to move to LA. Plus, drama with her neighbors in the apartment complex she was living in, and questions on topics like how to judge if a person is right for you, how to approach toxic family members, and what’s the deal with so many older people being friends with younger people? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the new LA phenomenon</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/02XjmR20GsjKGJKtAUCvDM</link>
      <guid>02XjmR20GsjKGJKtAUCvDM</guid>
      <description>The Saddle Ranch has morphed from a tacky Western-themed bar in LA that people rarely went to, to a TikToker, YouTuber, and paparazzi hot spot. Emma talks about why she kept going back (and how it wasn't good for her), getting filmed through an entire dinner, and chats about the paparazzi culture in LA. Plus, what's the most romantic thing someone's ever done for Emma? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the illusion of money</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3lEsnHVsLUgWwCz7c0q4bH</link>
      <guid>3lEsnHVsLUgWwCz7c0q4bH</guid>
      <description>Money can be a very tricky subject. When we don’t have it, it can seem like it will solve all of our problems. But when we get it, is it really all worth it? Emma gets super passionate this week, talking through her childhood growing up around people with a lot more money than her, how her perception changed when she started making money on her own, and why she wouldn’t change a thing. Plus, questions on saving, supporting others, and she clears the air on an article written about her when it came to money struggles. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>reading my diary</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7yCPFuH3mBE1RrS90c03C0</link>
      <guid>7yCPFuH3mBE1RrS90c03C0</guid>
      <description>Writing in a diary can be great for your mental health. It can also be great to look back and see how much you’ve changed. That’s exactly what Emma is doing this week. Analyzing old diary entries to understand why she felt a certain way, and how she’s grown. Why friendships don’t last long, manifesting things that aren’t good for us, and why it’s important to make mistakes. Plus, questions on the meaning of life, and why is cauliflower so damn good?  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice session #5</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1CMrX7doAdiQCqRtHiTvKB</link>
      <guid>1CMrX7doAdiQCqRtHiTvKB</guid>
      <description>You’re asking and Emma is answering. Lots of questions this week on topics like eating and body image issues, navigating toxic content on TikTok, and what to do if your significant other keeps liking provocative photos on social media. Plus, when is it right to take that next step in a relationship, and is body hair really that big of a deal? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>starting my own company</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/7y3Qb2m4rXqDtmCqyIAYIz</link>
      <guid>7y3Qb2m4rXqDtmCqyIAYIz</guid>
      <description>Starting a business has a ton of ups and downs, and Emma’s been through it all launching (and re-launching) her company and passion project Chamberlain Coffee. All of the trials and tribulations of getting a company up and running, from creating the product, creating the voice, branding, etc. Emma chats about it all and gives advice to anyone considering starting their own business as well. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>poop anxiety</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3YB1rcB7US8AySAey9Cqk9</link>
      <guid>3YB1rcB7US8AySAey9Cqk9</guid>
      <description>Emma went on a trip recently and stayed at a house with no locks on the doors… not ideal when you need to use the bathroom. Plus, finding ways to appreciate the illusions of Instagram, and the struggles of being social. And answering questions on how to know when you’re ready for a relationship, dealing with parents who probably shouldn’t be together, feelings toward cosmetic procedures, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i need to leave LA</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/62WeJ8RMln9vqmhWMa9PVH</link>
      <guid>62WeJ8RMln9vqmhWMa9PVH</guid>
      <description>Sometimes living in LA can be like living in your Instagram or TikTok feed. It sounds like fun, but it also makes it really difficult to disconnect. Dealing with that, and some anxieties that come with it. Plus, questions on healthy eating habits, ways to stay motived, dealing with panic attacks in a public place (like Coachella), and what to do if an ex has your nudes?  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>first kiss story</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0q629ud2Wm7LaAaQQQdDdk</link>
      <guid>0q629ud2Wm7LaAaQQQdDdk</guid>
      <description>For some of us, our first kiss was cute and fun. Emma’s experience was… a bit different. That, and so many more embarrassing stories: awkward dates, uncomfortable interactions with celebrities, and of course, accidental farts. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>why do i hate myself?</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/79JCwOU6AnKHHUghAjCirf</link>
      <guid>79JCwOU6AnKHHUghAjCirf</guid>
      <description>One of the more deep and emotional episodes of Anything Goes. Emma talks through her recent struggles with low self-esteem and self-confidence. What causes these feelings, the impact it has on us and people around us, and how we can get to a point where we’re comfortable in our own skin. Plus, answering a bunch of questions on relationships, how to tell if you’re in love, and will Emma ever do the WAP dance?? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice session #4</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3UNZWgjVnkS9uMyamOuCgD</link>
      <guid>3UNZWgjVnkS9uMyamOuCgD</guid>
      <description>Emma is back for another advice session answering everyone’s questions! From ways to forgive people who have wronged you, opening up to significant others about mental health, dealing with people shaming you for the number of people you’ve hooked up with, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>irrational fears</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5oJVB4uxistyNxhvtnCfzd</link>
      <guid>5oJVB4uxistyNxhvtnCfzd</guid>
      <description>You know that feeling, you lay down to go to sleep and all of your anxiety immediately hits you. Or, you stay up late worrying about something that’s completely irrational. Emma has experienced it all, shares some of her most irrational fears, and how to deal with them. Plus, thoughts on the paparazzi, how unpleasant her one and only surgery was, and a story she has NEVER told on the internet before. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>put your phone down</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2GSVqMBMAr2EzB9di0jDgN</link>
      <guid>2GSVqMBMAr2EzB9di0jDgN</guid>
      <description>Emma’s been off her phone for a while and feeling GREAT. Why it’s really helped with her anxiety and how it may help us all, too. Plus, insights into a new project (or two!) she’s working on, thoughts on TikTok potentially shutting down, how to deal with cheaters in relationships, and the three celebrities she’d want to be stranded on an island with. And is the blonde hair here to stay?? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>talking about nothing for an hour</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0bzLZ4AxDpHbPAmtv9L8bC</link>
      <guid>0bzLZ4AxDpHbPAmtv9L8bC</guid>
      <description>Anything really does go on this episode. Emma chats about everything from starting to surf, to taking a break from makeup, to why her jeans keep ripping. Plus, she answers a ton of questions like how much she’d let her future kids use the internet, all the bands and songs that would make up her life soundtrack (hint: there’s a lot), the things she loves most about her fans, and so much more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dealing with adults</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/57b9wWEpPhDgPIqmTEC1t7</link>
      <guid>57b9wWEpPhDgPIqmTEC1t7</guid>
      <description>As we grow up, our relationships with adults and “authority figures” can be complicated, intimidating, and confusing. In this episode, Emma discusses the types of relationships we have with the adults in our lives, how to effectively communicate with them, how to build strong and trusting relationships with parents, and everything in between. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the word &quot;irrelevant&quot; on the internet</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6akHvFmlbSjg29hM6Si25c</link>
      <guid>6akHvFmlbSjg29hM6Si25c</guid>
      <description>Emma goes deep this week on the notion of becoming “irrelevant” on the internet. Navigating “cancel culture”, challenges of growing up in front of millions, a lack of privacy and extra scrutiny, and less wiggle room to make normal teenage mistakes. Why clickbait content is less important than creating something you’re passionate about, and how living life based off views and likes can really be a strain on mental health. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>questions from guys</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/777yetovYpGTsU4hurJgaG</link>
      <guid>777yetovYpGTsU4hurJgaG</guid>
      <description>Emma is switching it up this week and answering questions from guys about girls. Everything you’ve ever wanted to know. Topics like how to recognize signs that a girl is into you, how to approach someone you like, great gift and date ideas, and jealousy in relationships. Plus, teaching guys all about periods, and answering the question that’s puzzled guys forever: why do girls all go to the bathroom together? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice session #3</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/44thnfmMHcqAC0ITtS89aG</link>
      <guid>44thnfmMHcqAC0ITtS89aG</guid>
      <description>Emma is back with more life advice for everyone. Topics like getting over an ex and how to deal with a friend starting to date them, thoughts on diets and the best ways to stay healthy, keeping a good relationship with your parents, especially if they are divorced, overcoming image issues and gaining self-confidence, and so much more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>gaining confidence</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/32XWDZ6doWPBRSKOg59zie</link>
      <guid>32XWDZ6doWPBRSKOg59zie</guid>
      <description>Breaking out of your shell and gaining confidence comes in different ways at different times for us all. Emma opens up about struggles with confidence growing up, and then eventually breaking out of her shell in various ways over the past few years, especially through YouTube. Plus, questions on things like making friends, talking with people you’re interested in, and how to be unapologetically yourself despite what others may think.  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>living alone</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2yV9wzoQMBkEQXMuFvX3ka</link>
      <guid>2yV9wzoQMBkEQXMuFvX3ka</guid>
      <description>Moving out is a big step in anyone’s life, but those responsibilities are such a drag. Emma dishes on the expectations vs. the realities of moving out and living on your own. From moving around to different locations, to doing all of your own cooking and cleaning, to meeting new people and missing your family. And when could it be time to move in with a significant other? Oh, and that leaky faucet isn’t going to fix itself. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pet peeves #1</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4zyFhDySDhcQQTXKCDPFxB</link>
      <guid>4zyFhDySDhcQQTXKCDPFxB</guid>
      <description>It’s a rant session. Emma is fired up about all of her pet peeves in this episode. From food chewing and getting it caught in the corner of your mouth (gross), to lying, judging and humble brags. Plus, maybe it’s time to get rid of that v-neck shirt, and she’s definitely judging that coffee order. And it’s finally been settled: which side of the roll should the toilet paper fall?  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>birthdays</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4RtPHXtGykQUGmKmxlFL2A</link>
      <guid>4RtPHXtGykQUGmKmxlFL2A</guid>
      <description>Most people (secretly) love their birthday. Emma is not one of those people. On this episode she dives into everything birthday related. Past birthday traumas, the 3 types of people on their birthday, awkwardness of giving and receiving gifts, anxiety about getting older, and everything in between. Does anybody actually like when people sing “happy birthday” to them? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>crazy LA stories</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1GZLsBEPkaAj0wag4irsZA</link>
      <guid>1GZLsBEPkaAj0wag4irsZA</guid>
      <description>Living in Los Angeles can be... interesting. Most people outside the city think of beautiful beaches and lavish celebrity mansions in the hills. And they do exist. But for those that live in the city, your view of it can be a bit different. Emma's lived in LA for a few years now, and has had her fare share of experiences. Everything from crazy people at fast food restaurants to what it's really like at those big parties. And she's STILL not over what someone did in her bathroom... Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice session #2</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2Z8OOPXPByhCUN427BVQCQ</link>
      <guid>2Z8OOPXPByhCUN427BVQCQ</guid>
      <description>Emma’s back with another advice session with issues we can all relate to! Topics like how to move on from an ex, workout routines and tips on eating healthy, believing in yourself when others may not, ways to stay close with people during quarantine, and so many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the future</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6F4dqAW2ASyY14qpW6gsPE</link>
      <guid>6F4dqAW2ASyY14qpW6gsPE</guid>
      <description>Most people want to get married and have kids some day because… it’s what you’re “supposed” to do… but is that right for everyone? Emma dives deep on it, from getting married, to divorce, to having kids and everything in between. What are the impending challenges of finding someone you’re supposed to spend the rest of your life with and raising children? How should you treat your kids when it comes to parties? And be honest, are babies actually cute? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>burnout</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1ZQ3vwOMyzaR9KaPhkyQ7Q</link>
      <guid>1ZQ3vwOMyzaR9KaPhkyQ7Q</guid>
      <description>We’ve all had that feeling of being burnt out: your brain is fried, you’re unmotivated, and you’re physically and mentally exhausted. Emma’s been there too. Whether it’s from school, YouTube, friendships, or life in general. She gets deep and personal on how to deal with burnout of all kinds, and how you can use it to come back better than ever. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>emotions</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2yrbmT9a56d6yltBf9AJiG</link>
      <guid>2yrbmT9a56d6yltBf9AJiG</guid>
      <description>Emotions, we all have them, and they can be a really tricky thing to navigate. Emma gets sensitive sometimes, as we all do, and she talks through it on this episode like a therapy session. From getting over people who wrong you, to worrying about relationships, letting yourself be vulnerable and opening up, why crying is actually good for us, and a lot more. Plus, Frankie the cat makes a (very short) cameo appearance on the podcast.   Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice session #1</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/2cABqMmn709E2hRBOSbltz</link>
      <guid>2cABqMmn709E2hRBOSbltz</guid>
      <description>One of Emma’s favorite things to do is give advice, so she’s dedicating the full episode to it based off your questions. From how to deal with crappy friendships, to food and fitness, to getting ghosted (it’s happened to all of us) and how to not be cringy when talking to someone you like. Emma is dishing on everything, nothing is off limits.   Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cheerleading</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/0V6PxqJbzxXHGOSxIvZDu1</link>
      <guid>0V6PxqJbzxXHGOSxIvZDu1</guid>
      <description>Maybe not all of us have cheered, but we’ve all been passionate about something, and had a competitive drive to push ourselves to be the best. But how much is too much? And how do we adjust when we’ve given up something we’ve been so dedicated to for so long? Emma talks through her cheerleading career, the ups and the downs, the lessons learned, and how it’s helped shape her. Plus, she finally gets started on Tiger King and is completely hooked like the rest of us!  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>intuitions</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/21PxqxOciFykXX3SfBl436</link>
      <guid>21PxqxOciFykXX3SfBl436</guid>
      <description>Gut feelings, instincts, that voice in the back of your head — we all have them. Sometimes they’re so strong they can’t be ignored. Should I be doing something different? Why don’t I fully trust this? Should this person be in my life? Emma dives deep into her intuitions, from important life decisions, to personal relationships, and everything in between. What to do with those intuitions, and when to trust them?  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>social media</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1YI86HOIHIV19kEuH17iEJ</link>
      <guid>1YI86HOIHIV19kEuH17iEJ</guid>
      <description>Social media. It’s in all of our lives. Most of the time, it can be used for good to connect us with each other. But sometimes, it can be a place of negativity and false realities that can really affect our wellbeing. Emma talks through her experiences with the ups and downs of social, dealing with things like body image issues, having unflattering photos of you spread around, and negative comments. She gives advice on how to handle it all, plus ways to practice healthy habits on social, and why she’s refusing to edit her photos on Instagram. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>high school</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/1A3HwSLAE2129RynMXNuHT</link>
      <guid>1A3HwSLAE2129RynMXNuHT</guid>
      <description>High school. For some it can be the best years of our lives, for others...not so much. Emma dishes on the entire high school experience and shares all of her embarrassing stories, from awkward interactions with boys, attempting to be athletic, and a self-inflicted hickey?!? Plus, she answers fan questions on high school and gives relationship advice to a few very interesting situations. And she may have been convinced to get a tattoo?? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>los angeles</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4L8qtma6H8k3Rc64EXX0yY</link>
      <guid>4L8qtma6H8k3Rc64EXX0yY</guid>
      <description>The city of angels. Either you love it or you hate it. Sometimes, both. Emma opens up about the pros and cons of the city - from living there, to the people you meet, to all of the things going on. Is everyone really obsessed with their appearance? Does LA really live up to the hype? Plus, why it's important to bring a quality people into your inner circle, to not worry about judgement, and to have confidence and be unapologetically yourself. Also, why you may want to consider wearing sweatpants to really nice restaurants from now on! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>fashion</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6j7FyIQoAM4aAVE1pZxmeI</link>
      <guid>6j7FyIQoAM4aAVE1pZxmeI</guid>
      <description>In this episode, Emma dives deep into one of her favorite interests - fashion. She discusses her early influences, tips for curating a great wardrobe on a budget, the importance of confidence, why she hates showing her neck, the secret to finding the perfect thrift store gem, and answers your questions. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>relationships</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/71zSr8DvNGcMvMMnGtkMqF</link>
      <guid>71zSr8DvNGcMvMMnGtkMqF</guid>
      <description>This week, Emma takes on the tricky topic of relationships. She gets into some of her past relationships, and how to deal with tough breakups and heartbreak. Plus, why you should consider being friends first, the importance of having time to yourself, and why having different views than your significant other isn’t a bad thing. Plus, she answers questions and gives some advice to fans on their relationship situations. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>failure</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/4kenABc1bd07E4k7pXDzCH</link>
      <guid>4kenABc1bd07E4k7pXDzCH</guid>
      <description>Emma opens up about changing the format of her podcast, how to deal with a perceived failure, not giving up, and ways to learn and grow from it. Plus, she talks about her decision to not go to college, the backlash she faced, and how it’s changed her life compared to other people her age. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>welcome to anything goes</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6USrEcuTpn46H8wcikCJSo</link>
      <guid>6USrEcuTpn46H8wcikCJSo</guid>
      <description>New podcast format, same Emma. Welcome to Anything Goes, an open and raw conversation on… well… anything. Got a question for Emma? Send them to @AGPodcast on Twitter, or leave her a voicemail at 567-ASK-EMMA (567-275-3662). New episodes every Thursday starting February 20th. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
